{
    "title": "CROCHET MESH SLEEVES CAC0140-035942M | January 11, 2024",
    "steps": [
        "CROCHET MESH SLEEVES CAC0140-035942M | January 11, 2024\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nABBREVIATIONS\nApprox = Dc = Double crochet Sp(s) = Space(s)\nApproximately Rep = Repeat St(s) = Stitch(es)\nBeg = Beginning RS = Right side Tog = Together\nCh = Chain(s) Sl st = Slip stitch WS = Wrong side\nMEASUREMENTS Ch 260 (multiple of 3 + 5).\nApprox 64\" [162.5 cm] wide from 1st row: [Right Side (RS)]. 1 double\ncuff-to-cuff by 21 (24)\" [53.5 (61) crochet (dc) in 8th chain (ch) from\ncm] long before sewing. hook (counts as skipped 2 ch, 1 dc,\nand ch-2). *Ch 2. Skip next 2 ch.\nGAUGE 1 dc in next ch. Repeat (rep) from\n16 sts and 7 rows = 4\" [10 cm] in * to end of chain. Turn. 86 dc and\npattern (pat). 85 ch-2 spaces (sps).\n2nd row: Ch 5 (counts as dc and\nINSTRUCTIONS\nch-2 sp here and throughout). Skip\nThe instructions are written for next ch-2 sp. 1 dc in next dc. *Ch 2.\nXS/S/M. If changes are necessary Skip next ch-2 sp. 1 dc in next dc.\nfor larger size the instructions will be Rep from * to end of row. Turn.\nwritten XS/S/M (L/XL/2XL). When Rep last row until work from\nonly one number is given it applies beginning (beg) measures\nMATERIALS to both sizes. approximately (approx) 10 (11½)\"\nCaron® Coconut Cakes™ (8 oz/227 g; 481 yds/440 m) [25.5 (29) cm], ending on a Wrong\nNotes: Side (WS) row.\nSizes XS/S/M L/XL/2XL\n• Ch 5 at beg of row counts as dc\nTutti-Frutti (84002) 2 2 cakes\nand ch-2 sp.\n614/561 700/640 yds/m • Sleeves are worked flat in\nSize U.S. 7 (4.5 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume® crochet hook or size one piece from front to back\nneeded to obtain gauge. Susan Bates® yarn needle. then seamed.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET MESH SLEEVES 1 of 2\nCROCHET MESH SLEEVES CAC0140-035942M | January 11, 2024\nShape neck opening: 1st row: FINISHING\n(RS). Ch 5. Skip next ch-2 sp. Place markers 20 (16½)\"\n1 dc in next dc. *Ch 2. Skip next [51 (42) cm] in from each side\nch-2 sp. 1 dc in next dc.** Rep along foundation chain and last\nfrom * 33 times more. Ch 44. row of work.\nSkip next 44 sts. 1 dc in next dc. Fold work in half lengthwise with\nNeck Opening made. Rep from * WS together (tog). Using Flat sl st,\nto ** 35 times more. Turn. 72 dc, join first and last rows tog from\n70 ch-2 sps, and 1 ch-44 sp. side edges to markers.\n2nd row: Ch 5. Skip next ch-2 sp. Weave in ends.\n1 dc in next dc. *Ch 2. Skip next\nch-2 sp. 1 dc in next dc.** Rep from\n* 34 times more. (Ch 2. Skip next\n2 ch. 1 dc in next ch.) 12 times.\nCh 2. Skip next 2 ch. 1 dc in next\ndc. Rep from * to ** 36 times more.\nTurn. 86 dc and 85 ch-2 sps.\n3rd row: Ch 5. Skip next ch-2 sp.\n1 dc in next dc. *Ch 2. Skip next\nch-2 sp. 1 dc in next dc. Rep from *\nto end of row. Turn.\nRep last row until work from FLAT SL ST JOINING DIAGRAM\nbeg measures approx. 21 (24)\"\n[53.5 (61) cm], ending on a RS row.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET MESH SLEEVES 2 of 2"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "CROCHET MESH SLEEVES CAC0140-035942M",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "January 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Approximately Rep = Repeat",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "260",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 + 5",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Approx 64",
            "label": "FAC"
        },
        {
            "text": "162.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "21",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "53.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "61",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "crochet",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "86",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "85",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M.",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M (L/XL/2XL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "only one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron® Coconut Cakes",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "481",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "25.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "29",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sizes XS/S/M L/XL/2XL\n• Ch",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Tutti-Frutti",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "84002",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2 2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "614/561",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Sleeves",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size U.S. 7",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4.5 mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET MESH",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "January 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "16½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "51",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "42",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "33",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "44",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 44",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck Opening",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "35",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "70 ch-2 sps",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch-44",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "34",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "36",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "86 dc and",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "85",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "FLAT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "21",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "53.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "61",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET MESH",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}