{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nCROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COCOON CAC0129-036441M | March 14, 2024\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nABBREVIATIONS\nApprox = Approximately Pat = Pattern\nBeg = Begin(ning)(s) Rep = Repeat\nCh = Chain(s) Rnd(s) = Round(s)\nDc = Double crochet RS = Right side\nHdc = Half double crochet Sl st = Slip stitch\nHdcbp = Yoh and draw up a loop Sp(s) = Space(s)\naround post of next stitch at back St(s) = Stitch(es)\nof work, inserting hook from right Tog = Together\nto left. Yoh and draw through WS = Wrong side\n3 loops on hook Yoh = Yarn over hook\nHdcfp = Yoh and draw up a look\naround post of next stitch at front\nof work, inserting hook from right\nto left. Yoh and draw through\n3 loops on hook\nSIZES INSTRUCTIONS\nTo fit chest measurement The instructions are written for\nXS/S/M 28-38\" [71-96.5 cm] XS/S/M/L. If changes are necessary\nL/XL/2XL 40-48\" [101.5-122 cm] for larger sizes the instructions will\nMATERIALS\n3/4/5XL 54-62\" [137-157.5 cm] be written XS/S/M/L (L/XL/2XL-\nCaron® Colorama Bamboo Blend™ (8 oz/227 g; 396 yds/363 m)\n3/4/5XL). Numbers for each size are\nSizes XS/S/M L/XL/2XL 3/4/5XL GAUGES\nshown in the same color throughout\nClear Sky (82008) 5 6 8 balls 14 sts and 8 rows = 4\" [10 cm] in the pattern. When only one number\n1620/1481.5 2315/2117 3010/2752 yds/m pat. is given in black, it applies to all sizes.\nSize U.S. H/8 (5 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume® crochet hook or size\nneeded to obtain gauge. Susan Bates® stitch markers. Susan Bates®\nyarn needle.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COCOON 1 of 3\nCROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COCOON CAC0129-036441M | March 14, 2024\nNotes: 4th rnd: Sl st in first ch-3 sp. Ch 6. Cuffs Ribbing",
        "Ch 3 at beg of rnd counts as dc. 3 dc in same sp as last sl st. (Ch 1. With RS facing, join yarn with sl st With RS facing, join yarn with sl st",
        "Ch 2 at beg of rnd does not 3 dc) in each ch-1 sp to next corner to Armhole at side seam. to Front opening at side centre\ncount as hdc. ch-3 sp. *Ch 1. (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) in 1st rnd: Ch 2. Work 48 hdc evenly back seam.\ncorner ch-3 sp. (Ch 1. 3 dc) in each around entire armhole opening. 1st rnd: Ch 2. Work even amount\nMOTIF (make 4 alike) ch-1 sp to next corner ch-3 sp. Join with sl st to first hdc. of hdc evenly around entire Front\nNote: Ch 6 at beg of rnds counts Rep from * twice more. Ch 1. 2 dc 2nd rnd: Ch 2. 1 hdcfp in first hdc. opening. Join with sl st to first hdc.\nas 1 dc and ch 3. in first ch-3 sp. Join with sl st to *1 hdcbp around next hdc. 1 hdcfp 2nd rnd: Ch 2. 1 hdcfp around first\n3rd ch of ch 6. around next hdc. Rep from * to last hdc. *1 hdcbp around next hdc.\nCh 5. Join with sl st to first ch to Rep last rnd until Motif measures hdc. 1 hdcbp around last hdc. Join 1 hdcfp around next hdc. Rep from\nform a ring. approx 19½ (20½-21½)\" [49.5 (52- with sl st to first hdcfp. * to last hdc. 1 hdcbp around last\n1st rnd: Ch 6. (3 dc. Ch 3) 3 times in 54.5) cm] square. Fasten off. 3rd rnd: Ch 2. 1 hdcfp in first hdc. Join with sl st to first hdcfp.\nring. 2 dc in ring. Join with sl st to hdcfp. *1 hdcbp around next 3rd rnd: Ch 2. 1 hdcfp around\n3rd ch of ch 6. [Four groups of 3 dc, Assembly hdcbp. 1 hdcfp around next hdcfp. first hdcfp. *1 hdcbp around next\nfour ch-3 sps forming corners]. See Diagrams on page 3. Rep from * to last hdcbp. 1 hdcbp hdcbp. 1 hdcfp around next hdcfp.\n2nd rnd: Sl st in first ch-3 sp. Ch 6. Sew 4 Motifs tog using a flat seam around last hdcbp. Join with sl st Rep from * to last hdcbp. 1 hdcbp\n3 dc in same sp as last sl st. *Ch 1. to form a square. Fold work in half to first hdcfp. around last hdcbp. Join with sl st\n(3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) in next ch-3 sp. with WS facing and seam at top. Rep 3rd rnd until work from beg to first hdcfp.\nRep from * twice more. Ch 1. 2 dc Place markers 8\" [20.5 cm] down measures approx 3\" [7.5 cm]. Rep 3rd rnd until work from beg\nin first ch-3 sp. Join with sl st to from fold at each side. Sew side measures approx 3\" [7.5 cm].\n3rd ch of ch 6. seams from marker to bottom Fasten off.\n3rd rnd: Sl st in first ch-3 sp. Ch 6. using flat seam.\n3 dc in same sp as last sl st. Ch 1.\n3 dc in next ch-1 sp. *Ch 1. (3 dc.\nCh 3. 3 dc) in next ch-3 sp. Ch 1.\n3 dc in next ch-1 sp. Rep from *\ntwice more. Ch 1. 2 dc in first\nch-3 sp. Join with sl st to 3rd ch of\nch 6.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COCOON 2 of 3\nCROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COCOON CAC0129-036441M | March 14, 2024\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COCOON 3 of 3"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "March 14, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Pat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sl st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Hdcbp",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M 28-38",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "71-96.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "101.5-122 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3/4/5XL",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "54-62",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "137",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M/L (L/XL/2XL-\n",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Colorama Bamboo",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "396",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3/4/5XL",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sizes XS/S/M L/XL/2XL 3/4/5XL GAUGES",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Clear Sky",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "82008",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "only one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2315/2117 3010/2752 yds",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "pat.",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COCOON",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "March 14, 2024\nNotes",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Cuffs Ribbing\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Armhole",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "48",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "approx 19½",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "20½-21½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "49.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "last\n1st",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "54.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3rd",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Four",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Assembly",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "four",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sew 4 Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "st Rep",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 hdcbp\n",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COCOON",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "March 14, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COCOON",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}