{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nCROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN RHC0829-37675M | November 11, 2024\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nABBREVIATIONS\nBeg = Beginning Sc = Single crochet\nCh = Chain(s) Sl st = Slip stitch\nCont = Continue(ity) Sp(s) = Space(s)\nDc = Double crochet St(s) = Stitch(es)\nHdc = Half double crochet Tog = Together\nRep = Repeat Tr = Treble crochet\nRnd(s) = Round(s) WS = Wrong side\nRS = Right side Yoh = Yarn over hook\nMATERIALS\nSizes XS/S/M/L XL/2/3XL\nRed Heart® All in One™ Granny Square™ (8.8 oz/250 g; 417 yds/381 m)\nContrast A 3 3 balls\nSoft White – Spring Serene (2045) 30 42 Squares\nContrast B 4 4 balls\nSoft White – Peachy Keen (2042) 33 39 Squares\nRed Heart® Super Saver® (7 oz/198 g; 364 yds/333 m)\nContrast C Soft White (0316) 2 3 balls\n680/619 750/683 yds/m\nSizes U.S. H/8 (5 mm) and U.S. I/9 (5.5 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume®\ncrochet hooks or size needed to obtain gauge. Susan Bates® yarn\nneedle.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN 1 of 4\nCROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN RHC0829-37675M | November 11, 2024\nSIZES • When Motif is complete, cut 3rd rnd: Sl st in next ch-3 sp. Ch 6. ASSEMBLY\nTo fit chest measurement yarn where Color 5 (longest 3 dc in same ch-3 sp. *Ch 1. 3 dc in Note: Join Motifs tog using\nXS/S/M 28-42\" [71-106.5 cm] color rep) ends, leaving a tail for next ch-1 sp. Ch 1. (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) Contrast C as shown in diagrams\nL/XL/2XL 44-54\" [112-137 cm] weaving in. in next ch-3 sp. Rep from * twice on page 4.\n• Begin next Motif with Color 1 more. Ch 1. 3 dc in last ch-1 sp.\nApprox finished chest and repeat 5 rnds for each Motif. Ch 1. 2 dc in first ch-3 sp. Join. Size XS/S/M/L only: Sleeves are\n(with edging) • Ch 3 at beg of rnd counts as dc. 4th and 5th rnds: Sl st in next joined separately then sewn into\nBody after Body is assembled. Note\nXS/S/M 50\" [127 cm] • Ch 6 at beg of rnds counts as dc ch-3 sp. Ch 6. 3 dc in same ch-3 sp.\nfolded Motifs on side seams of\nL/XL/2XL 62\" [157.5 cm] and ch-3 sp. *(Ch 1. 3 dc) in each ch-1 sp to next\nBody will leave a 24\" [61 cm] square\n• Join all rnds with sl st to 3rd ch of ch-3 sp. Ch 1.** (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc)\nGAUGE ch-6 unless otherwise indicated. in next ch-3 sp. Rep from * twice total armhole opening for sleeves\non each side (see shaded sections\nMotif = 6\" [15 cm] square with more, then from * to ** once. 2 dc\non diagram for square armhole\nlarger hook. Size XS/S/M/L - make 30 Motifs in first ch-3 sp. Join. Fasten off.\nsleeve placement).\nwith A; 33 Motifs with B – 63 total.\nINSTRUCTIONS\nAll Sizes: Join Motifs: Hold RS of\nGRANNY SQUARE MOTIF Size XL/2/3XL - make 42 Motifs\n2 Motifs facing each other with sts\nNotes: with A; 39 Motifs with B – 81 total.\naligned. With larger hook, join using\n• Motifs begin with Color 1\nContrast C with sl st in ch-2 corners\n(shortest color rep) from center With larger hook and Color 1, ch 4.\nof aligned Motifs at top right. With\nof pull-skein, leaving a 4\" [10 cm] Join with sl st to first ch to form\nRS facing each other, following\ntail to weave in. ring.\ndiagrams, join Motifs, matching\n• Each color aligns with 1 rnd in 1st rnd: (RS). Ch 6. (3 dc. lettered sides and working rows\nthe Motif with 5 colors in total. Ch 3) 3 times in ring. 2 dc in ring. of sl st loosely through both\nIf too much color is left at end Join. thicknesses. Fasten off.\nof rnd, pull back some sts and 2nd rnd: Sl st in next ch-3 sp. Ch 6.\nslightly loosen gauge to re-work 3 dc in same ch-3 sp. *Ch 1. (3 dc. Sleeve Edging: 1st row: (RS). With\nsts and finish at color change. If Ch 3. 3 dc) in next ch-3 sp. Rep smaller hook, join C with sl st in\ntoo little color is left, pull back from * twice more. Ch 1. 2 dc in first lower edge of Sleeve and work\nsome sts and slightly tighten ch-3 sp. Join. 38 sc evenly across. Turn.\ngauge to re-work sts and finish 2nd to 6th rows: Ch 1. 1 sc in each\nat color change. sc to end of row. Turn.\nFasten off. Sew sides of Sleeve\nEdging.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN 2 of 4\nCROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN RHC0829-37675M | November 11, 2024\nLower Edging: 1st row: (RS). With\nsmaller hook, join C with sl st in\nlower edge of Left Front corner and\nwork sc evenly across lower edge to\ncorner of Right Front. Turn.\n2nd to 6th rows: Ch 1. 1 sc in each\nsc to end of row. Turn. Fasten off.\nCollar and Front Band: 1st row:\n(RS). With smaller hook, join C with\nsl st in lower edge of Right Front\nand work sc evenly up Right Front,\nacross back neck and down Left\nFront. Turn.\n2nd row: Ch 2 (does not count as\nhdc). 1 hdc in each sc to end of row.\nTurn.\n3rd row: Ch 2. Working into\nhorizontal loop lying below next st\n(see diagram), work 1 hdc in each\nhdc to end of row. Turn.\nRep last row until Collar and Front\nBand measures 8\" [20.5 cm].\nFasten off.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN 3 of 4\nCROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN RHC0829-37675M | November 11, 2024\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN 4 of 4"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN RHC0829-37675",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "crochet St(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Granny Square",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8.8 oz/250",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "417",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Soft White",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2045",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "30",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "42 Squares",
            "label": "PERCENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "4 4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Soft White",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "33",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "39 Squares",
            "label": "PERCENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "7 oz/198",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "364",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "0316",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2 3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "680/619 750/683 yds",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5.5 mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN 1",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN RHC0829-37675",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Color 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "1. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M 28-42",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "71-106.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "112-137 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Begin",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Approx",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size XS/S/M/L",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "127 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "6. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "157.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "24",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "61 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Join",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size XS/S/M/L - make",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "30",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "33",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "63",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "All Sizes",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "42",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "39",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "81",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Color 1\nContrast C",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Color 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Join",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sleeve",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "38",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sleeve\nEdging",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Lower Edging: 1st row: (RS",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Left Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Right Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Right Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Right Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front\nBand",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY SQUARE COATIGAN 4",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}