{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nCROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI RHC0829-37681M | November 11, 2024\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nABBREVIATIONS\nApprox = Approximately Rep = Repeat\nBeg = Beginning Rnd(s) = Round(s)\nCh = Chain(s) RS = Right side\nDc = Double crochet Sl st = Slip stitch\nDc2tog = [Yoh, insert hook in Sp(s) = Space(s)\nnext space, yoh, draw up a loop, St(s) = Stitch(es)\nyoh, draw yarn through 2 loops Tog = Together\non hook] twice, yoh, draw yarn WS = Wrong side\nthrough 3 loops on hook. Yoh = Yarn over hook\nPM = Place marker\nSIZES INSTRUCTIONS\nTo fit chest measurement The instructions are written for size\nMATERIALS XS/S/M 28-38\" [71-96.5 cm] XS/S/M. If changes are necessary\nL/XL/2XL 40-48\" [101.5-122 cm] for larger sizes the instructions\nSizes XS/S/M L/XL/2XL 3/4/5XL\n3/4/5XL 50-62\" [127-157.5 cm] will be written XS/S/M (L/XL/2XL-\nRed Heart® All in One™ Granny Square™ (8.8 oz/250 g; 417 yds/381 m)\n3/4/5XL). Numbers for each size are\nMain Color (MC) 2 3 4 balls\nFinished Square shown in the same color throughout\nBlack-Amber Moss (2040) 28 40 54 Squares (before assembly) the pattern. When only one number\nContrast A 1 1 1 ball XS/S/M 36\" [91.5 cm] square. is given in black, it applies to all\nBlack-Scarlet Sands (2041) 8 9 10 Squares L/XL/2XL 42\" [106.5 cm] square. sizes.\n3/4/5XL 48\" [122 cm] square.\nRed Heart® Super Saver® (7 oz/198 g; 364 yds/333 m)\nContrast B Black (0312) 1 1 1 ball GAUGE\n147/134 192/175 250/229 yds/m Motif = Approximately (approx)\n6\" [15 cm] square.\nSize U.S. I/9 (5.5 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume® crochet hook or size\nneeded to obtain gauge. Susan Bates® yarn needle. Susan Bates®\nstitch markers.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI 1 of 6\nCROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI RHC0829-37681M | November 11, 2024\nNotes: Starting with color 1, ch 4. Join with 4th and 5th rnds: Sl st in next Assembly\n• Motifs begin (beg) with Color 1 sl st to first ch to form ring. ch-3 sp. Ch 6. 3 dc in same ch-3 sp. Seaming with Flat Sl St Join: (RS).\n(shortest color repeat (rep)) from 1st rnd: (Right Side [RS]). Ch 6. *(Ch 1. 3 dc) in each ch-1 sp to next With B, sl st Motifs together (tog)\ncenter of pull-skein, leaving a (3 dc. Ch 3) 3 times in ring. 2 dc in ch-3 sp. Ch 1.** (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) following Layout Diagrams on pages\n4\" [10 cm] tail to weave in. ring. Join. in next ch-3 sp. Rep from * twice 4, 5 and 6, working through back\n• Each color aligns with 1 round 2nd rnd: Sl st in next ch-3 sp. Ch 6. more, then from * to ** once. 2 dc loops only and keeping working\n(rnd) in the Motif with 5 colors 3 dc in same ch-3 sp. *Ch 1. (3 dc. in first ch-3 sp. Join. Fasten off. yarn to Wrong Side (WS) of work to\nin total. If too much color is left Ch 3. 3 dc) in next ch-3 sp. Rep create a flat sl st chain detail on RS\nat end of rnd, pull back some from * twice more. Ch 1. 2 dc in first of work (see Diagram).\nstitches (sts) and slightly loosen ch-3 sp. Join.\ngauge to re-work sts and finish 3rd rnd: Sl st in next ch-3 sp. Ch 6.\nat color change. If too little color 3 dc in same ch-3 sp. *Ch 1. 3 dc\nis left, pull back some sts and in next ch-1 sp. Ch 1. (3 dc. Ch 3.\nslightly tighten gauge to re-work 3 dc) in next ch-3 sp. Rep from *\nsts and finish at color change. twice more. Ch 1. 3 dc in last ch-1\n• When Motif is complete, cut yarn sp. Ch 1. 2 dc in first ch-3 sp. Join.\nwhere Color 5 (longest color rep)\nends, leaving a tail for weaving\nin. Beg next Motif with Color 1\nFLAT SL ST JOINING DIAGRAM\nand rep 5 rnds for each Motif.\nMOTIF Note: Keep working yarn to WS of\nWith MC make 28 (40-54) work so only flat sl st chain is visible\nWith A make 8 (9-10) on RS.\nNotes: Following Assembly Diagram on\n• Chain (ch) 3 at beg of rnd counts page 3, fold work in half, WS tog.\nas double crochet (dc). Place markers (PM) 8\" [20.5 cm],\n• Ch 6 at beg of rnds counts as dc down from fold at each side. With\nand ch-3 space (sp). B, flat sl st sides tog from marker to\n• Join all rnds with slip stitch bottom. Keep markers in place.\n(sl st) to 3rd ch of ch-6 unless\notherwise indicated.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI 2 of 6\nCROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI RHC0829-37681M | November 11, 2024\nFINISHING Cuff Edging\nEdging Join B with sl st to Armhole\nNotes: Opening at marker.\n• Ch 3 at beg of rnd counts as dc. 1st rnd: Ch 1. 1 sc in each st (dc\n• With RS facing, join B with and/or ch-sp) around. Join with sl st\nsl st to Front Opening at side to first sc.\nseam in corner ch-3 sp (see 2nd and 3rd rnds: Ch 1. 1 sc in\nAssembly Diagram). each sc around. Join with sl st to\nfirst sc.\n1st rnd: Ch 3. *(Ch 1. 3 dc in next Fasten off.\nch-1 sp) 4 times. Ch 1. 1 dc in next Rep for 2nd armhole opening.\nch-3 sp. dc2tog over same ch-3 sp Remove markers. Weave in all ends.\nand next ch-3 sp. 1 dc in last\nch-3 sp worked. Rep from * around\nto last motif. (Ch 1. 3 dc in next\nch-1 sp) 4 times. Ch 1. 1 dc in next\nch-1 sp. Dc2tog over same ch-3 sp\nand first ch-3 sp. Join with sl st to\ntop of ch-3.\n2nd rnd: Sl st in next ch-1 sp. Ch 3.\n2 dc in same ch-1 sp as join. *Ch 1.\n3 dc in next ch-1 sp. Rep from *\naround. Ch 1. Join with sl st to top\nof ch-3.\n3rd rnd: Ch 1. 1 sc in each st (dc\nand/or ch-sp) around. Join with sl st\nto first sc.\nFasten off.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI 3 of 6\nCROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI RHC0829-37681M | November 11, 2024\nLAYOUT DIAGRAMS: XS/S/M\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI 4 of 6\nCROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI RHC0829-37681M | November 11, 2024\nLAYOUT DIAGRAMS: L/XL/2XL\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI 5 of 6\nCROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI RHC0829-37681M | November 11, 2024\nLAYOUT DIAGRAMS: 3/4/5XL\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY COCOON CARDI 6 of 6"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0829-37681M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sl st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "MATERIALS XS/S/M 28-38",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "71-96.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "101.5-122 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sizes XS/S/M L/XL/2XL 3/4/5XL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "50-62",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "127",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M (L/XL/2XL-\n",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Granny Square",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8.8 oz/250",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "417",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3/4/5XL",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Main Color",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Finished Square",
            "label": "FAC"
        },
        {
            "text": "Black-Amber Moss",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "2040",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "28",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "only one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M 36",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "91.5 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Black-Scarlet Sands",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2041",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "106.5 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3/4/5XL 48",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "122 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Red Heart",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7 oz/198",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "364",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Contrast B Black",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "0312",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "147/134 192/175",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size U.S.",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5.5 mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0829-37681M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Layout Diagrams",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Wrong Side",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Diagram",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Color 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "28",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "40-54",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "9-10",
            "label": "TIME"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Chain",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Join",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0829-37681",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Ch",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "and/or ch-sp",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front Opening",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Assembly Diagram",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "dc2tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Dc2tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0829-37681M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M\nFor",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0829-37681M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0829-37681M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "November 11, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3/4/5XL",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}