{
    "title": "MAKE THIS",
    "steps": [
        "MAKE THIS\nCROCHET SNOOD\nBlack\nSoft\nWhite\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nRHC0116-034200M\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER | CROCHET SNOOD | MAKE THIS\nNOVEMbER 16, 2023 | PG 1\nCOPYRIGHT © 1996-2023 SPINRITE YARNS ONLINE INC. | ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.\nMAKE THIS\nWHAT YOU’LL NEED\nYARN\n• Red Heart® Super Saver®\n(7 oz/198 g; 364 yds/333 m)\nCOLORS\nQuantity\n• Contrast A Black (0312)\n2 balls or 530 yds/482 m\n• Contrast B Soft White (0316)\n1 ball or 55 yds/50 m\nTOOLS\n• Size U.S. L/11 (8 mm) Susan Bates®\nSilvalume® crochet hook or size\nneeded to obtain gauge.\nGAUGE\n• Susan Bates® yarn needle.\n8 double crochet (dc) and 5 rows =\n4\" [10 cm] with 2 strands of yarn held • 3\" [7.5 cm] wide piece of cardboard\ntogether. for tassels.\n• Tape measure.\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nRHC0116-034200M\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER | CROCHET SNOOD | MAKE THIS\nNOVEMbER 16, 2023 | PG 2\nCOPYRIGHT © 1996-2023 SPINRITE YARNS ONLINE INC. | ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.\nABBREVIATIONS\nBeg = Beginning Rep = Repeat\nCh = Chain(s) Rnd = Round\nDc = Double crochet Sl st = Slip stitch\nRem = Remaining Tog = Together\nMAKE THIS\nINSTRUCTIONS MEASUREMENTS\n60\" [152.5 cm] around x 10\" [25.5 cm]\nwide.\nUSING THIS GUIDE\nClick on the underlined words\nthroughout the pattern to access our\nlibrary of helpful tools.\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nRHC0116-034200M\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER | CROCHET SNOOD | MAKE THIS\nNOVEMbER 16, 2023 | PG 3\nCOPYRIGHT © 1996-2023 SPINRITE YARNS ONLINE INC. | ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.\nABBREVIATIONS\nBeg = Beginning Rep = Repeat\nCh = Chain(s) Rnd = Round\nDc = Double crochet Sl st = Slip stitch\nRem = Remaining Tog = Together\nMAKE THIS\nINSTRUCTIONS\nHolding 2 strands of A together (tog), make a slip knot and place\nit on the hook.\nSlip knot\nMake a loop with yarn and fold it on itself to make a pretzel shape.\nThen draw through to make slip knot.\nChain (ch) 120.\nChain\n*Yarn over hook (Yoh),\npull through loop – 1 chain made.\nRepeat (rep) from * 119 times more\n– 120 chains made.\nJoin with slip stitch (sl st) in first ch, taking care not to twist ch.\nSlip stitch\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nInsert hook into first ch. Yoh and pu ll the yarn through both the\nwork and the loop on the hook in one movement.\nRHC0116-034200M\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER | CROCHET SNOOD | MAKE THIS\nNOVEMbER 16, 2023 | PG 4\nCOPYRIGHT © 1996-2023 SPINRITE YARNS ONLINE INC. | ALL RIGHTS RESERVED.\nABBREVIATIONS\nBeg = Beginning Rep = Repeat\nCh = Chain(s) Rnd = Round\nDc = Double crochet Sl st = Slip stitch\nRem = Remaining Tog = Together\nMAKE THIS\nINSTRUCTIONS\n1st round (rnd): Ch 3 (counts as\ndouble crochet - dc). 1 dc in each ch around.\nJoin with sl st to top of ch 3. 120 dc.\nDouble crochet\nYoh and insert hook into next ch and draw up a loop.\nYoh and draw through first 2 loops on hook.\nYoh and draw through remaining (rem) 2 loops on hook – 1 dc made.\nRep last steps in each ch around - 120 dc made.\n2nd rnd: Ch 3. 1 dc in each dc around. Join with sl st to top of ch 3.\nRep last rnd 10 times more. Fasten off at end of last rnd.\nTo fasten off the yarn, cut yarn leaving a long tail. Pull end through\nloop on hook and pull gently to tighten.\nWeave in all yarn tails.\nFINISHING\nTassels (Make 6)\nHolding 1 strand each of A and B tog, wrap yarn around\na 3\" [7.5 cm] piece of cardboard 10 times. Tie securely\nat one end. Cut across other end. Wrap yarn 3 times\naround tassel 1\" [2.5 cm] from tied end. Fasten securely.\nTrim tassels to approx 2\" [5 cm] length.\nAttach Tassels to Snood, having 3 on either side edge, evenly\nspaced.\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nWe love seeing your makes!\nShare your photos using #YARNSPO and tag us\n@yarnspirations on Instagram or find us on Facebook.\nRHC0116-034200M\nCROCHET | SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER | CROCHET SNOOD | MAKE THIS\nNOVEMbER 16, 2023 | PG 5\nCOPYRIGHT © 1996-2023 SPINRITE YARNS ONLINE INC. | ALL RIGHTS RESERVED."
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "BEGINNER",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "16, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1996-2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "YARNS ONLINE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7 oz/198",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "364",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "0312",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "530 yds/482 m\n• Contrast B Soft White",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "0316",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "55",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "8 mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "BEGINNER",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "16, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1996-2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "YARNS ONLINE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sl st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Remaining Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "152.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "25.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "BEGINNER",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "16, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1996-2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "YARNS ONLINE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sl st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Remaining Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "120",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Repeat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "119",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "120",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "BEGINNER",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "16, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1996-2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "YARNS ONLINE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sl st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Remaining Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "around - 120",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Attach Tassels",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "YARNSPO",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Instagram",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "BEGINNER",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "16, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1996-2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "YARNS ONLINE",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}