{
    "title": "CROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY",
    "steps": [
        "CROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nRIPPLE HAT & SCARF | CROCHET SHOP KIT\nGAUGE: 14 sts (2 repeats) = 3½”; 6 rows = 4” in pattern.\nCHECK YOUR GAUGE. Use any size hook to obtain\nthe gauge.\nSPECIAL ABBREVIATIONS:\nCL2: Yo and draw up a lp in next dc, yo and draw through\n2 lps, skip next 2 sc, yo and draw up a lp in next dc, yo\nand draw through 2 lps, yo and draw through all 3 lps rem\non hook.\nCL3: Yo and draw up a lp in next st, yo and draw through 2\nlps, skip next 3 sts, yo and draw up a lp in next st, yo and\ndraw through 2 lps, yo and draw through all 3 lps rem on\nhook.\nShell: (2 dc, ch 3, 2 dc) all in st or sp indicated.\nSCARF\nWith CA, ch 281.\nRnd 1 (Right Side): Sc in 2nd ch from hook, * ch 1, skip\nnext 2 ch, shell in next ch, ch 1, skip next 2 ch, sc in next\nch **, sc in next ch; rep from * across, end at **; turn to\nwork on opposite side of beg ch; sc in same ch as last sc;\nrep from * across, end at ** changing to CB in last sc; join\nwith a sl st to first sc – 40 ch-3 sps on each side.\nRnd 2: With CB, ch 1, sc in same sc as joining, sc in ch-1\nsp, ** ch 3, dc in next 2 dc, shell in ch-3 sp, dc in next dc, *\nCL2, dc in next dc, shell in ch- 3 sp, dc in next dc; rep from\n*across first side; dc in next dc, ch 3, sc in ch-1 sp **, sc in\nnext 2 sc, sc in ch-1 sp; rep from ** to ** across next side;\nRipple Hat sc in last sc changing to CC; join.\nRnd 3: With CC, ch 1, sc in same sc as joining, sc in next\n& Scarf sc, sc in ch-3 sp, ** ch 3, skip next 2 dc, dc in next 2 dc,\nshell in ch-3 sp, dc in next dc, * CL3, dc in next dc, shell\nin ch-3 sp, dc in next dc; rep from * across first side; dc in\nnext dc, ch 3, skip next 2 dc, sc in ch-3 sp **, sc in next 4\nDesigned by Mary Jane Protus. sc, sc in ch-3 sp; rep from ** to ** across next side; sc in\nlast 2 sc changing to CA; join.\nHat fits most women. Scarf measures Rnd 4: With CA, ch 1, sc in same sc as joining and next 2\napproximately 6” x 71”. sc, 2 sc in ch-3 sp, ** ch 3, skip next 2 dc, dc in next 2 dc,\nshell in ch-3 sp, dc in next dc, * CL3, dc in next dc, shell\nRED HEART® “Soft Yarn”: 1 Ball each 3720 Lavender in ch-3 sp, dc in next dc; rep from * across first side; dc in\nCA, 2541 Blue Sky CB, and 4601 Off White CC next dc, ch 3, skip next 2 dc, 2 sc in ch-3 sp **, sc in next 6\nsc, 2 sc in ch-3 sp; rep from ** to ** across next side; sc in\nCrochet Hook: 5.5mm [US I-9]. last 3 sc; join. Fasten off.\nYarn needle.\nFor more ideas & inspiration —\n©2009 Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box 12229 www.redheart.com www.coatsandclark.com\nGreenville, SC 29612-0229\nwww.crochettoday.com www.knitandcrochettoday.com\nRHC0138-023736M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 2019 RIPPLE HAT & SCARF | CROCHET 1 of 2\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nRIPPLE HAT & SCARF | CROCHET\nHAT\nWith CC, ch 4; join with sl st in first ch to form ring.\nRnd 1: Ch 3, 13 dc in ring; join with sl st in top of ch-3 –\n14 sts.\nRnd 2: Ch 3, dc in same st as joining, [2 dc in next dc]13\ntimes; join – 28 sts.\nRnd 3: Ch 3, [2 dc in next dc, dc in next dc] 13 times, 2 dc\nin last dc; join – 42 sts.\nRnd 4: Ch 3, [2 dc in next dc, dc in next dc] 20 times, 2 dc\nin last dc; join – 63 sts.\nRnd 5: Ch 1, sc in same st as joining, * ch 1, skip next 2\ndc, shell in next dc, ch 1, skip next 2 dc, sc in next dc **, sc\nin next dc; rep from * around, end at **; join in first sc – 9\nch-3 sps.\nRnd 6: Sl st in sp, sl st in next 2 dc, ch 3, * shell in ch-3 sp,\ndc in next dc, CL2 **, dc in next dc; rep from * around end\nat ** and working 2nd leg of CL2 in first dc of previous rnd;\njoin in top of ch-3.\nRnd 7: St in next 2 dc, ch 3, * shell in ch-3 sp, dc in next\ndc, CL3 **, dc in next dc; rep from * around end at ** and\nworking 2nd leg of CL3 in first dc of previous rnd; join.\nRep Rnd 7 four more times. Fasten off.\nBrim-Next Rnd: With WRONG SIDE facing (this will be\nthe right side when brim is turned up), attach CA in 2nd dc\nof shell; ch 3, * shell in ch-3 sp, dc in next dc, CL3 **, dc\nin next dc; repeat from * around end at ** and working 2nd\nleg of CL3 in first dc of previous rnd; join. Fasten off.\nRep last rnd 6 more times in following color sequence:\n[CB, CC, CA] twice.Weave in ends.\nRED HEART® “Soft Yarn”, Art. E728\nsolids - 5 oz, 256 yds; prints - 4 oz, 204 yds\nABBREVIATIONS: beg = beginning; CA, CB,\nCC = Colors A, B, C; ch = chain; dc = double crochet;\nlp(s) = loop(s); mm = millimeters; pat = pattern;\nrep = repeat; rnd = round; sc = single crochet; sl st = slip\nstitch; sp(s) = space(s); st(s) = stitch(es); yo = yarn over;\n* or ** = repeat whatever follows the * or ** as indicated;\n[ ] = work directions in brackets the number of times\nspecified.\nFor more ideas & inspiration —\n©2009 Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box 12229 www.redheart.com www.coatsandclark.com\nRHC0138-023736M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 2019 RIPPLE HAT & SCARF | CROCHET 2 of 2\nGreenville, SC 29612-0229\nwww.crochettoday.com www.knitandcrochettoday.com"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "RIPPLE HAT & SCARF",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yo",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shell",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "281",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 1",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ripple Hat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "CC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "CC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 4",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Mary Jane Protus",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "last 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "Scarf",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 4",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "71",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3720",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "2541",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Blue Sky CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4601",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 6",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "last 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2009",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0138-023736M",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "RIPPLE HAT & SCARF",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RIPPLE HAT & SCARF",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 1: Ch",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "28",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "42",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 4",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "63",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 5: Ch 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CL3 **",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CL3",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rep Rnd 7",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "four",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CL3",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CL3",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "E728",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "256",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "204",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2009",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "RHC0138-023736M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "RIPPLE HAT & SCARF",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        }
    ]
}