{
    "title": "Scarf measures 5” (12.5 cm) wide x 60” Fringe",
    "steps": [
        "Scarf measures 5” (12.5 cm) wide x 60” Fringe\n(152.5 cm) long Cut twenty-eight 16” (40.5 cm) strands of A\nand fourteen 16” (40.5 cm) strands of B.\nDirections for hat are given in adult size Using 2 strands of A and 1 strand of B for\nSmall. Changes for Large are in parentheses each fringe, fold fringe strands in half and pull\nfolded end through corner sc on one end of\nHat measures 18 (21)” (45.5 [53.5] cm) in Scarf, pull tails through loop and pull tightly.\ncircumference, to fit 20 (22)” (51 [56] cm) Attach 6 more fringes evenly spaced across\nCROCHET\nhead same end of Scarf. Attach 7 fringes evenly\nSKILL LEVEL\nEASY spaced across other end of Scarf.\nSPECIAL STITCH\nDesigned by J. Erin Boland Long single crochet (Lsc): Sc in top of next dc HAT\n2 rows below. With A, ch 4; join with a slip st in first ch to\nform ring.\nWhat you will need: SCARF Round 1 (right side): Ch 3 (counts as dc here\nWith A, ch 16. and throughout), work 11 (13) dc in ring; join\nRED HEART® Super Saver®:\nRow 1: Dc in 4th ch from hook and in each ch with a slip st in top of beginning ch-3—12\n2 skeins of 3931 Grape Fizz A, and\nacross, turn—14 dc. Beginning ch-3 counts (14)dc.\n1 skein of 387 Soft Navy B\na sdc. Round 2: Ch 3, dc in first st, 2 dc in each st\nSusan Bates® Crochet Hook: Row 2-3: Ch 3 (counts as dc here and around; join with a slip st in top of beginning\n6mm [US J-10] throughout), dc in each st across, turn. ch-3—24 (28) dc.\nRow 4: Ch 1, sc in first st and in each st Round 3: Ch 3, dc in first st, dc in next st,\nGAUGE: 12 dc = 4”, 6 rows\nacross, turn—14 sc. Fasten off A, join B. *2 dc in next st, dc in next st; repeat from *\nin pattern = 4”. CHECK YOUR\nGAUGE. Use any size hook to Row 5: With B, ch 1, sc in first 2 sts, *Lsc in around; join with a slip st in top of beginning\nobtain the gauge given. next dc 2 rows below, sc in each of next 2 sts; ch-3—36 (42) dc.\nrepeat * across, sc in last st, turn—10 sc; 4 Round 4: Ch 1, sc in first st and in each st\nLsc. Fasten off B, join A. around; join with a slip st in first sc.\nRow 6-8: Repeat Row 2. Fasten off A.\nRED HEART® Super Row 9: Repeat Row 4. Fasten off A, join B. Round 5: With right side facing, join B with sc\nSaver®, Art. E300 Row 10: Repeat Row 5. in any st, *Lsc in next st**, sc in next st; repeat\navailable in solid color Repeat Rows 6-10, maintaining color from * around, ending last repeat at **; join\n7 oz (198 g), 364 yd (333 m); Jagged Lines Hat\nsequences until scarf measures 58” (147.5 with a slip st in first sc. Fasten off B.\nmulticolor, heather and print 5 oz\ncm)ending with Row 10 of pattern. Round 6: With right side facing, join A with a\n(141 g), 244 yd (223 m), flecks 5 oz\n(141 g), 260 yds (238 m) skeins & Scarf Set Repeat Row 2 twice. slip st in any st, ch 3, dc in same st, dc in next\nLast row: Repeat Row 4. st, *2 dc in next st, dc in next st; repeat from\nFasten off. *around join with a slip st in top of beginning\nHere’s a hat and scarf pattern that uses long ch-3—54 (63) dc.\nsingle crochets to accent the basic stitches. FINISHING Round 7: Ch 3, dc in each st around; join with\nChoose colors that are in similar color Weave in ends. a slip st in top of beginning ch-3.\nContinued...\nfamilies for this interesting effect.\nSHOP KIT\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: www.redheart.com\n©R2H0C140 1C3o8a-ts0 1&9 C6l7ar7kM | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 JAGGED LINES HAT & SCARF SET | CROCHPEaTg e 11 ooff 22\nRound 8: Ch 1, sc in first st and in each st\naround; join with a slip st in first sc. Fasten\noff A.\nRound 9: With B, repeat Round 5. Fasten off\nB, join A.\nRounds 10-11: Repeat Round 7.\nRounds 12-13: Repeat Rounds 8-9.\nRound 14-17: Repeat Rounds 10-13.\nRounds 18-20: Repeat Rounds 10-12 once.\nFasten off.\nFINISHING\nWeave in ends.\nABBREVIATIONS\nA, B = Color A, B; ch = chain; dc = double\ncrochet; sc = single crochet; st(s) = stitch(es);\n( ) = work directions in parentheses into\nsame st; [ ] = work directions in brackets the\nnumber of times specified; * or ** = repeat\nwhatever follows the * or ** as indicated.\nRedHeart.com\nRHC0138-019677M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 JAGGED LINES HAT & SCARF SET | CROCHET 2 of 2\nFind more ideas & inspiration: www.redheart.com\nPage 2 of 2\n©2014 Coats & Clark"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "Scarf",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "12.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "152.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "40.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "fourteen 16",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "40.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "B.\nDirections",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "21",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "53.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Scarf",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "51",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "56",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Scarf",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Scarf",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "J. Erin Boland Long",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "HAT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RED HEART®",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3931",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Grape Fizz A",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "387",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2-3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch-3—24",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "28",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "st",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch-3—36",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "42",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6-8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "B. Round 5",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Saver®",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Repeat",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "6-10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "198",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "364 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "333",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Lines Hat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "58",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "147.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "141",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "244 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "223",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "141",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "260",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "238",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "& Scarf Set Repeat Row",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "st",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch-3—54",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "63",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1&9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "C6l7ar7kM",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "JAGGED LINES HAT & SCARF",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Round 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "10-11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Repeat Round 7",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10-13",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "18-20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "=",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "JAGGED LINES HAT & SCARF",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2014",
            "label": "DATE"
        }
    ]
}