{
    "title": "Directions are for size Small; changes for For All Sizes",
    "steps": [
        "Directions are for size Small; changes for For All Sizes\nsizes Large are in parentheses Next Round: Dc in each dc around.\nRepeat last round until piece measures 6”\nHat Circumference: 20 (22)” (51 (56) cm) [15cm] from beginning, end 3 sts before\nScarf measures 6” x 60”, (15 cm x 152.5 cm) beginning marker, hdc in next st, sc in next st,\nslip st in last st.\nNOTE Fasten off.\nHat is worked in continuous rounds, working\nCROCHET\nSKILL LEVEL in back loops only of each st throughout. SCARF\nEASY Scarf is worked in front loops of only of each Ch 22.\nst throughout. Row 1: Working in front loops only, dc in 4th\nDesigned by Linda Dean ch from hook and in each ch across – 20 dc.\nHAT Row 2: Ch 1, turn, working in front loops only,\nCh 4, slip st to first ch to form a ring. sc in each st across.\nWhat you will need: Round 1: Ch 3 (counts as dc here and Row 3: Ch 3, turn, dc in each st across.\nthroughout), work 11 dc into ring – 12 dc. Repeat last 2 rows until piece measures 60”\nRED HEART® Boutique Treasure™:\nPlace marker for beginning of round. [152.5cm], end with Row 2.\n3 balls 1918 Abstract, 1901\nRound 2: Working in back loops only Fasten off.\nMosaic, or 1913 Spectrum\nthroughout, 2 dc in each dc around – 24 dc.\nSusan Bates® Crochet Hook: Round 3: [2 dc in next st, dc in next dc] FINISHING\n6mm [US J-10] around – 36 dc. Weave in ends.\nRound 4: [2 dc in next st, dc in next 2 dc]\nStitch marker, yarn needle\naround – 48 dc. Abbreviations\nGAUGE: 12 sts = 4” [10cm]; 9 Round 5: [2 dc in next st, dc in next 3 dc] ch = chain; dc = double crochet; hdc = half\nrows/rounds = 4” [10cm]. CHECK around – 60 dc. double crochet; mm = millimeters; sc = single\nYOUR GAUGE. Use any size hook crochet; st(s) = stitch(es); [ ] = work directions\nto obtain the gauge.\nFor Large Size Only in brackets the number of times specified.\nRound 6: [2 dc in next st, dc in next 9 dc]\nBuy Yarn around – 66 dc.\nRED HEART® Boutique\nTreasure™ Art E788 Igloo Snail Hat\navailable in 3.5 oz\n(100 g), 151 yds\n(138 m) balls and Scarf\nThis clever hat is crocheted without joining\nthe rounds and reminded the designer of a\nsnail’s shell…thus the name, Snail Hat. Add a Colors from left to right:\n1918 Abstract, 1901 Mosaic\nscarf for the perfect set to warm you. This is\nor 1913 Spectrum\na superb gift set idea!\nSHOP KIT\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: www.redheart.com and www.crochettoday.com\nRHC0138-020661M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 IGLOO SNAIL HAT AND SCARF | CROCHET 1 of 1\n©2013 Coats & Clark"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "For All Sizes",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Hat Circumference",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "51",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Scarf",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15 cm x",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "152.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Linda Dean",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "20 dc",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "152.5cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1901",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1913",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "st",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "6mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "st",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "9 Round 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "st",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "st",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 9",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art E788",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "100",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "151",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "138",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Scarf",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Snail Hat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1918",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1901",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Mosaic\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1913",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2013",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\n",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}