{
    "title": "Crocheted Baby Set",
    "steps": [
        "Crocheted Baby Set\nNaptime\nLW1311\nPattern FREE with RED HEART yarn purchase!\nNaptime Yoke:Ch 1,sc in first sc;[draw up a lp in next 2 sc,yo and\ndraw yarn through both lps on hook–decmade] 15 times,\nLW1311HH sc in next 2 sc,[dec,dec,dec,sc in next sc] 9 times,sc in\nnext 2 sc,[dec] 15 times,sc in last sc – 72 sc.\nHHIntermediate experience required. Divide for Fronts and Back-Left Front:Ch 1,sc in first 17\nDesigned by Mary Jane Protus. sc;turn.Work even in sc until 41/4\" above division,end\nwrong side row.Shape Neck:Ch 1,work across first 15 sc;\nBlanket measures 39\" x 39\".Robe fits infant 0-3 months; turn.Dec 1 sc at neck edge on next 2 rows.Work a few rows\nhat circumference 14\". even until 51/2\" above division. Fasten off. Back: With\nRED HEART®“Soft Baby”,Art.E705,(7 ounce solid/6 wrong side facing,join yarn and sc in next 38 sc;turn.Work\nounce multi-color skeins):Blanket:14 Ounces 7964 Naptime even in sc until same length as Left Front.Fasten off.\nCA,8 ounces 7881 Powder Blue CB.Robe & Hat:10 Ounces Right Front:With wrong side facing,join yarn and sc in\n7964 Naptime CA,6 ounces 7881 Powder Blue CB. last 17 sc.Complete same as for Left Front,reversing\nneck shaping.\nCrochet Hook:U.S.Size H-8 [5mm].\nEleven 1/2\"buttons;sewing needle and thread;yarn needle. Sleeves:With CBch 50.Work Rows 1-12 same as for Blanket\nover 49 sts,then rep Rows 3-12 once,then Row 3 once more.\nGAUGE:In pat—16 sts = 31/2\";20 rows = 51/2\".CHECK Fasten off.Cuff-Row 1:With right side facing,join CBon\nYOUR GAUGE.Use any size hook to obtain the gauge. opposite side of beg ch;ch 1,sc in first st,* skip next st,sc in\nnext st;rep from * across;turn – 25 sc.Rows 2-4:Ch 1,sc in\nBLANKET:With CB,ch 178.Row 1 (Right Side):Sc in each sc across;turn.Row 5:Ch 1,sc in first sc,skip next sc,*\n2nd ch from hook and in each ch across;turn – 177 sc. (sc,ch 3,sc) all in next sc,skip next sc;rep from * to last sc;sc\nRow 2:Ch 1,sc in each sc across changing to CAin last sc. in last sc.Fasten off.Sew sleeve and cuff seam.\nRow 3:With CA,ch 1,sc in first sc,* sc in next sc,ch 1,skip\nnext sc,hdc in next sc,ch 1,skip next sc,dc in next sc,[ch 1,skip Finishing:Sew shoulder seams.Set in sleeves.With right side\nnext sc,tr in next sc] twice,ch 1,skip next sc,dc in next sc,ch facing,attach CBat lower edge of right front;ch 1,sc even-\n1,skip next sc,hdc in next sc,ch 1,skip next sc,sc in next sc **, ly up right front,around neck edge and down left front;turn.\nch 1,skip next sc;rep from * to last sc,end at **;sc in last sc; Work 5 rows sc across left front only for button band.Fasten\nturn. off.Buttonhole Band:Mark positions for 11 buttonholes\nRow 4:Ch 1,sc in each st and sp across;turn. across right front edge.With wrong side facing,attach CBat\nRow 5:Rep Row 3 changing to CBin last sc. neck edge of right front;ch 1,sc down right front edge;turn.\nRow 6:With CB,ch 1,sc in first sc,* sc in next (sc,sp,hdc, Work 1 more row sc.Buttonhole Row:Ch 1,[sc to marker,\nsp,dc,[sp,tr] twice,sp,dc,sp,hdc,sp,sc) **;draw up a lp ch 2,skip 2 sc] 11 times,sc to end;turn.Next Row:Ch 1,[sc\nin sc 4 rows below next sc,yo and draw through both lps to sp,2 sc in sp] 11 times,sc to end.Work 1 more row sc.Next\non hook–long scmade;rep from * to last sc,end at **;sc Row:Rep Row 5 of Sleeve Cuff up right front,around neck,\nin last sc;turn. and down left front,adjusting as necessary around neck and\nRow 7:Ch 1,sc in each st across changing to CAin last sc. at corners.Fasten off.Sew on buttons.\nRow8:Ch 4,skip first sc,* tr in next sc,ch 1,skip next sc,dc\nHAT:With CB,ch 66.Work even in sc over 65 sts for 11\nin next sc,ch 1,skip next sc,hdc in next sc,[ch 1,skip next sc,\nrows,then work Rows 3-12 twice same as Blanket,then\nscin next sc] twice,ch 1,skip next sc,hdc in next sc,ch 1,skip\nRow 3 once more.Shape Crown:Ch 1,sc in first sc,sc in\nnext sc,dc in next sc,ch 1,skip next sc,tr in next sc **,ch 1,\neach sp across,sc in last sc;turn.Next Row:Ch 1,sc in first\nskip next sc;rep from * to last sc,end at **;tr in last sc;turn.\nsc,* skip next sc,sc in next sc;rep from * across.Fasten\nRow 9:Rep Row 4.\noff.Weave yarn through rem sts, gather tightly, fasten\nRow 10:Rep Row 8 changing to CBin last sc.\nsecurely.With wrong side facing (will be right side when\nRow 11:With CB,ch 1,sc in first tr,* sc in next (tr,sp,dc,sp,\nbrim is turned up) attach CBand work Row 5 of Sleeve\nhdc,sp,sc),long sc,sc in (sc,sp,hdc,sp,dc,sp,tr,sp);rep from\nCuff across rem lps of beg ch.Sew back seam,reversing\n*across working last sc in top of ch-4 instead of sp;turn.\nfor brim.Weave in ends.\nRow12:Rep Row 7.\nRep Rows 3-12 twelve moretimes,then Rows 3-7 again;\nnow turn and work sc evenly down side edge with CB. ABBREVIATIONS:beg=begin(ning);ch=chain;dc=double cro-\nFasten off.With right side facing,attach CBand work 1 row chet; hdc = half double crochet; mm = millimeters; rem =\nsc along opposite side edge;ch 1,now work 1 rnd sc around remain(ing);rep=repeat;rnd=round;sc=single crochet;sl=slip;\nsp=space;st(s)=stitch(es);tr=treble crochet;yo=yarn over;*or\nentire blanket;join to first sc.Fasten off.Weave in ends.\n**=repeat whatever follows the * or ** as indicated;[]=work\nROBE:With CA,ch 130.Work Rows 1-12 same as for directions in brackets the number of times specified.\nBlanket over 129 sts,then rep Rows 3-12 six moretimes,\nthen Rows 3 and 4 again.\n©2001 COATS & CLARK Inc, Greer, SC, 29650\nwww.coatsandclark.com Printed in USA1101"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "RED HEART",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "15",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "15",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "HHIntermediate",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Mary Jane Protus",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shape Neck",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "39",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "0-3 months",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 38 sc;turn",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Left Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7881",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Powder Blue CB.Robe & Hat:10 Ounces",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7881",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Powder Blue CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "last 17",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Left Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "49",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "51/2\"",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Cuff-Row",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBon",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "178.Row 1",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "177",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CAin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,skip Finishing:Sew",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBat",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc even-\n1,skip",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Buttonhole Band",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBat",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Buttonhole Row",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2,skip 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "last sc;turn",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "CAin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Row8",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Blanket",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "last sc;turn",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "last sc;turn",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBand",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Cuff",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "twelve",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBand",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 row",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,now",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "blanket;join",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "129",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "six",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2001",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "COATS & CLARK Inc",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greer",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29650",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "USA1101",
            "label": "GPE"
        }
    ]
}