{
    "title": "Poncho & Hat",
    "steps": [
        "Poncho & Hat\nRnds 12-21:Rep Rnd 3, changing to CBin last dc\nof Rnd 21. Cut CA.\nRnds 22-24:With CBrep Rnd 3. Fasten off.\nLW1448 Easy\nNeckband-Rnd 1:With right side facing, smaller\nOne size fits most women. Poncho measures\nhook, and working on opposite side of beg ch, join\n231/ 2\" long from shoulder to hem and 63\"\nCBin any lp, ch 1, sc in each lp around; join with\naround at loweredge. Hat circumference is 21\".\na sl st to first sc – 40 sc.\nRED HEART®Bulky Weight Yarn. These models\nRnds 2-5:Ch 1, sc in each sc around; join.\nmade in RED HEART®“Light & Lofty™”,100%\nacrylic, Art. E708 (6 ounce/140 yard solid; 4.5 Fasten off at end of Rnd 5. Weave in ends.\nounce/105 yard multicolor skeins).\nAmount-Poncho: 18 Ounces No. 9334 Café Au HAT\nLait CAand 5 ounces No. 9316 Puff CB. Hat:2 Brim:With largerhook and CB, ch 34; join with a\nOunces CAand 3 ounces CB. sl st to form a ring, being careful not to twist ch.\nCrochet Hooks: 10mm [US N-15] and 11.5mm Rnd 1:Ch 1, sc in first ch, dc in next ch, * sc in\n[US P-16]. next ch, dc in next ch; rep from * around; join with\na sl st to first sc; turn– 34 sts.\nGAUGE:In dc– 5 sts = 3\"; 4 rnds = 4\" with small- Rnd 2:Ch 1, sc in first dc, dc in next sc, * sc in next\ner hook. In sc– 5 sts = 3\"; 8 rnds = 4\" with small- dc, dc in next sc; rep from * around noting that last\ner hook. CHECK YOUR GAUGE. Use any size dc is worked into same sc as joining of previous\nhook to obtain the gauge given. rnd; turn.\nRep Rnd 2 until 7\" from beg, changing to CAin last\nPONCHO\nst of last rnd, do not turn.\nWith smaller hook and CA, ch 40; join with a sl st\nto form a ring, being careful not to twist ch. Crown: Next Rnd (Right Side):Change to smaller\nhook, ch 1, sc in each st around inc 1 st; do not join\nRnd 1:Ch 1, 2 sc in first ch, sc in next 7 ch, * 2 sc\nbut mark end of rnd by placing a contrasting thread\nin next ch, sc in next 7 ch; rep from * around; join\nbetween the last and first sts – 35 sc. Do not turn.\nwith a sl st to first sc – 45 sc.\nWork even in rnds of sc for 31/ 2\".\nRnd 2:Ch 3, dc in same sc as joining, dc in next 2\nShape Top: [Draw up a lp in next 2 sc, yo and\nsc, * 2 dc in next sc, dc in next 2 sc; rep from *\ndraw through all 3 lps on hook– dec made; sc in\naround; join with a sl st to top of ch-3 – 60 sts.\nnext 3 sc] 7 times – 28 sc.\nRnds 3 and 4:Ch 3, dc in each dc around; join to\nNext Rnd:[Dec, sc in next 2 sc] 7 times – 21 sc.\ntop of ch-3.\nNext Rnd:[Dec, sc in next sc] 7 times – 14 sc.\nRnd 5:Ch 3, dc in same ch as joining, dc in next 3\ndc, * 2 dc in next dc, dc in next 3 dc; rep from * Next Rnd:[Dec] 7 times – 7 sc; sl st in next sc.\naround; join – 75 sts. Fasten off.\nRnds 6 and 7: Rep Rnd 3. Weave yarn through remaining sts, draw up tightly\nand fasten securely. Fold brim in half to the right\nRnd 8:Ch 3, dc in same ch as joining, dc in next 4\nside.\ndc, * 2 dc in next dc, dc in next 4 dc; rep from *\naround; join – 90 sts.\nABBREVIATIONS:beg= begin(ning); ch= chain; dc= double\nRnds 9 and 10:Rep Rnd 3. crochet; dec= decrease; lp(s)= loop(s); mm= millimeters; rep=\nrepeat; rnd= round; sc= single crochet; sl st= slip stitch; st(s)=\nRnd 11:Ch 3, dc in same ch as joining, dc in next\nstitch(es); *= repeat whatever follows the * as indicated.\n5 dc, * 2 dc in next dc, dc in next 5 dc; rep from *\naround; join – 105 sts.\n©2004 COATS & CLARK, P.O. Box 12229, Greenville, SC, 29612-0229\nwww.coatsandclark.com Printed in USA1104"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "Poncho & Hat\nRnds",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rep Rnd 3",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 21",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Easy\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neckband",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "231/ 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "63",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "21",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RED HEART®“Light & Lofty",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "18 Ounces",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "5 ounces",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "9316",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Puff CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Hat:2 Brim",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "34",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hooks",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "11.5mm Rnd 1:Ch 1",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "P-16",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "34",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rep Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "CAin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "40",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crown",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 1:Ch 1",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 7",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 7",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "35",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "31/ 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "28",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Next Rnd:[Dec",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "21",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Next Rnd:[Dec",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 5:Ch 3",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "75",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 4",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 4",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "90",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "beg=",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "9 and 10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rep Rnd 3",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "crochet",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 11",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "5 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 5",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "105",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2004",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "COATS & CLARK",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "P.O. Box 12229",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "www.coatsandclark.com Printed",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}