{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nGIRL'S CROCHET PONCHO BRC0307-002035M | February 3, 2023\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nSIZE Rep from * to * 5 times more. Join\nOne Size to fit Child 8/10 yrs. with sl st in top of ch 3. (13 groups\nof 3 dc between each V-point).\nTo fit chest measurement 3rd rnd: Sl st in each of next 2 dc\n26-28\" [66-71 cm]. and next ch-1 sp. Ch 3 (counts as\ndc). 2 dc in same sp as last sl st.\nGAUGE Ch 1. *3 dc in next ch-1 sp. Ch 1.*\n12 sc and 13 rows = 4\" [10 cm]. Rep from * to * to marked V-point\nch-1 sp. (3 dc. Ch 1. 3 dc in V-point\nINSTRUCTIONS ch-1 sp. Rep from * to * to next\nNote: Poncho is worked in one marked V-point ch-1 sp. (3 dc.\npiece from neck edge down. Ch 1) twice in V-point ch-1 sp. Rep\nfrom * to * to end of rnd. Join with\nCh 94. Join with sl st to first ch to sl st to top of ch 3.\nform ring, taking care to not twist Rep last rnd until work from beg\nchain. measures approx 16\" [40.5 cm].\n1st rnd: Ch 1. 1 sc in each ch Fasten off.\naround. Join with sl st to first sc.\nMATERIALS 94 sc. Drawstring: Make a chain 50\"\n2nd rnd: Ch 3 (counts as dc). [127 cm] long. Fasten off. Beg at\nBernat® Pop!™ (5 oz/140 g; 280 yds/256 m)\n1 dc in each of next 2 sc. Ch 1. center Front, weave drawstring\nViolet Vision (84007) 3 balls\nSkip next sc. *1 dc in each of next through ch-1 sps of 2nd rnd at\nSize U.S. H/8 (5 mm) Susan Bates® crochet hook or size needed to obtain 3 sc. Ch 1. Skip next sc.* Rep from neck edge.\ngauge. 2 Susan Bates® Split-Lock Stitch Count Markers. * to * 4 times more. 3 dc in next\nsc. Ch 1 for center front V-point\nABBREVIATIONS\n(place marker on this ch-1 sp). 3 dc\nApprox = Approximate(ly) Rnd(s) = Round(s)\nin next sc. Ch 1. Skip next sc. Rep\nBeg = Begin(ning) RS = Right side\nfrom * to * 11 times. 3 dc in next\nCh = Chain(s) Sc = Single crochet sc. Ch 1 for center back V-point\nDc = Double crochet Sl st = Slip stitch (place marker on this ch-1 sp). 3 dc\nRep = Repeat Sp(s) = Space(s) in next sc. Ch 1. Skip next sc.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. GIRL'S CROCHET PONCHO 1 of 1"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO BRC0307-002035",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "February 3, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "SIZE Rep",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Child 8/10",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "26",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "66",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Poncho",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 94",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "40.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "50",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "127 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Beg",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Bernat®",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "5 oz/140",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "280",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Violet Vision",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "84007",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "obtain 3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Split-Lock Stitch Count Markers",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sl st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GIRL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}