{
    "title": "Caron International Yarns and Latch Hook Kits 12/12/2007 01:53 PM",
    "steps": [
        "Caron International Yarns and Latch Hook Kits 12/12/2007 01:53 PM\nSubscribe to Caron Connections, our free e-newsletter.\nEnter your e-mail address\nsubscribe\nCaron Yarns\nSimply Soft®\n\"The Gift\"\nSimply Soft® Baby NEW\nSimply Soft® Brites\nPoncho\nSimply Soft® Heather\nNEW with\nSimply Soft® Quick\nSimply Soft® Tweed\nSimply Soft® Shadows Designed by Dee Neer\nBliss TECHNIQUE USED: Crochet\nCraft & Rug Yarn NEW\nFelt-It\nClick to enlarge image\nFling\nschematics\nGlimmer\nSIZES\nNatura®\nX-Small/Small (Medium, Large/X-Large)\nPrinter Friendly PDF\nOne Pound\nPerfect Match®\nFINISHED MEASUREMENTS\nPizazz®\nLength: 18 (20, 22), plus scalloped edge\nWintuk®\nLower edge: approximately 72 (80, 88)\"\nMATERIALS\nCaron Latch Hook Kits\nCaron International Simply Soft\nShaggy\n(100% acrylic; 6 oz/172g, approx 330 yds/304m):\nCaron® Classics\n3 (3, 3) skeins #9742 grey heather;\nNatura®\n3 (3, 3) skeins #9703 bone\nWonderArt®\nuse 1 strand of each held together throughout\nKrafty Kids™\nCrochet hook size US K/10.5 (6.5mm),\nChristmas designs\nor size to obtain gauge\nTapestry ndl (tn);\nstitch markers (optional)\nBuy all your favorite\nCaron products online\nGAUGE\nUsing size US K/10.5 (6.5mm) hook, in St patt: 10 sts and 6 rows = 4\"/10cm;\nScallops measure approx 4\" wide x 3\" deep\nSTITCHES USED\nChain (ch)\nDouble crochet (dc)\nReverse single crochet (rev sc)\nSingle crochet (sc)\nSlip stitch (sl st)\n2 x 1 Cluster Stitch (multiple of 3 sts +2; 2-row repeat)\nRow 1: Ch 4 (counts as dc, ch 1), * skip next 2 dc, work 2 dc in next ch-1 space\nhttp://www.caron.com/projects/ss/gift_poncho.html Page 1 of 3\nCaron International Yarns and Latch Hook Kits 12/12/2007 01:53 PM\nRow 1: Ch 4 (counts as dc, ch 1), * skip next 2 dc, work 2 dc in next ch-1 space\n(cluster made), ch 1; repeat from * across, end dc in top of beginning ch, turn.\nRow 2: Ch 3 (counts as dc), dc in ch-1 space, * ch 1, skip next 2 dc, work 2 dc in\nnext ch-1 space; repeat from * across, turn.\nFan Pattern (multiple of 10 sts; 3-rows)\nFoundation Row: Beginning approx 2\" from center Back point (corner of short\nedge and long edge which hangs down), join yarn with a sl st, ch 1, work 5 sc to\ncorner, ch 1, then working into corner st a second time, sc around, join with a sl\nst to beginning ch; work 133 (150, 166) sc along long edge of original piece, work\n26 (29, 33) sts total along short end—160 (180, 200) sts, with the ch-1 at corner\nbeing the center of the first fan.\nRow 1: Ch 1, skip first sc, sc in next 3 sc, ch 1, skip 1 sc, work 5 dc in corner ch-\n1 (fan made), * ch 1, skip 1 sc, sc in next 7 sc, ch 1, skip 1 sc, work 5 dc in next\nsc (fan); repeat from * around, end ch 1, skip 1 sc, sc to beginning of rnd, join\nwith sl st to beginning ch.\nRow 2: Ch 1, skip first sc, sc in next sc, * ch 2, skip next [2 sc, ch-1], work 2 dc in\neach dc of fan, ch 2, skip next [ch-1, 2 sc], sc in next 3 sc; repeat from * around,\nend last repeat ch 2, skip next [ch-1, 2 sc], join with a sl st to beginning ch.\nRow 3: Ch 3, skip next [sc, ch-2], * in fan, work [* 2 dc in next dc, dc in next dc;\nrepeat from * around fan], ch 3, skip next [ch-2, sc], sc in next sc, ch 3, skip next\n[sc, ch-2]; repeat from * around, end last repeat ch 3, sl st in beginning ch.\nFasten off.\nNOTE: Poncho is worked from the lower edge to upper edge as a large\nrectangle; the Scalloped edging is worked after Poncho is sewn together. There\nis actually no Back or Front to this Poncho – it may be worn with the pointed end\nin Back or in Front for 2 entirely different looks. References to Back and Front are\nfor clarification of the instructions only.\nPONCHO\nLoosely ch 136 (154, 169).\nFoundation Row: Beginning in 4th ch from hook, dc in next ch, ch 1, skip 1 ch,\ndc in next 2 ch; repeat from * across, end dc in last 2 ch—134 (152, 167) sts,\nturn.\nBegin 2 x 1 Cluster Stitch; work even until piece measures 18 (20, 22)\" from the\nbeginning.\nFasten off.\nFINISHING\nReferring to schematic and Diagram, measure along lower edge 18 (20, 22)\";\nplace a marker (pm). Fold piece, matching points Y to Y and Z to Z; neatly sew\nseam.\nNeck Edging: Row 1: Beginning at lower edge of V-neck (center Back), join\nyarn, ch 1, work 1 row sc evenly around neck edge, join with a sl st to beginning\nch. DO NOT TURN.\nRow 2: Working from left to right, work 1 row rev sc evenly around neck.\nFasten off.\nLower Edging: Work Foundation Row of Fan patt, working 160 (180, 200) sc\naround entire lower edge.\nWork Rows 1 – 3 of Fan patt once.\nFasten off. Weave in ends.\nhttp://www.caron.com/projects/ss/gift_poncho.html Page 2 of 3\nCaron International Yarns and Latch Hook Kits 12/12/2007 01:53 PM\n|| Yarns || Free Projects || Where to Buy || Links || Learning || Contact Us || Caron Connections || News || Latch\nHook ||\nVisit Bond America online ©2007 Caron International\nhttp://www.caron.com/projects/ss/gift_poncho.html Page 3 of 3"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "Caron International Yarns",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Latch Hook Kits",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "01:53 PM",
            "label": "TIME"
        },
        {
            "text": "Subscribe",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron Connections",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron Yarns",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Simply Soft®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "The Gift",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Simply Soft®",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Simply Soft",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Simply Soft",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Dee Neer\nBliss",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet\nCraft & Rug Yarn",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Natura",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "X-Small/Small (Medium, Large/X-Large",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Printer Friendly PDF",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20,",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "approximately 72",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "80,",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "88",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron Latch Hook Kits\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shaggy",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "100%",
            "label": "PERCENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "330",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron® Classics",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9742",
            "label": "MONEY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Natura®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9703",
            "label": "MONEY"
        },
        {
            "text": "WonderArt®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Krafty Kids",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "6.5mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Christmas",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "6.5mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "St",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4\"/10cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2-row",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron International Yarns",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Latch Hook Kits",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "01:53 PM",
            "label": "TIME"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fan Pattern",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "second",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "133",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "150",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "166",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "26",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "29",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "33",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "180",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "200",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 7",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Poncho",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "Poncho",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "136",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "154",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "169",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "last 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "152",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "167",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20, 22",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Diagram",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "20, 22",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 row",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 row",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Lower Edging: Work Foundation Row of Fan",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "160",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "180",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "200",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron International Yarns",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Latch Hook Kits",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "01:53 PM",
            "label": "TIME"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarns || Free Projects",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2007",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron International",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}