{
    "title": "One size fits most.",
    "steps": [
        "One size fits most.\nCape measures 20” (51 cm) x 48” (122 cm).\nNOTE: Cape is worked in 2 panels.\nCAPE\nPanel A\nWith A, ch 30.\nCROCHET\nRow 1: Working in back loops only, tr in 4th ch\nSKILL LEVEL\nEASY hook and each ch across.\nRows 2-48: Ch 4 (counts as tr here and\nDesigned by Double Stitch Twins. throughout), turn, tr in each tr across– 27 tr.\nWhat you will need: Fasten off.\nRED HEART® Super Tweed:\nPanel B\n1 skein 7708 Pinkberry A.\nWith B, make as for Panel A.\nand RED HEART® Super Saver:\n1 skein 360 Cafe Latte B.\nFINISHING\nSusan Bates® Crochet Hook: With wrong sides together, hold one long edge\n5mm [US H-8].\nof each Panel together, join B in first st and\nworking through both layers, sc evenly spaced\n2 buttons, 1” (25mm) diameter,\nyarn needle. along edges of rows to join Panels.\nFasten off.\nGAUGE: 11 tr = 4” (10 cm); 4 Sew buttons on right side of Panel A 7”\nrows = 4” (10 cm ). CHECK YOUR\n(18 cm) from one short end.\nGAUGE. Use any size hook to\nWeave in ends.\nobtain the gauge.\nBuy Yarn Abbreviations: A, B, C = Color A, B, C; ch =\nRED HEART® Super\nchain; mm = millimeters; sc = single crochet;\nSaver® Art. E300\nst(s) = stitch(es); tr = triple or treble crochet; *\navailable in solid color\n7 oz (198 g), 364 yd or ** = repeat whatever follows the * or ** as\n(333 m); multicolor, heather and Convertible Cape indicated.\nprint 5 oz (141 g), 244 yd (223 m),\nflecks 5 oz (141g), 260 yds (238\nm)skeins. Two garments in one! Choose your favorite\nway to wear this unique wrap, choose your\nRED HEART® Super\nTweed®, Art. E779, favorite colors to fit your wardrobe. It’s so fast\nBuy Yarn\navailable in tweed\nand easy to make, you’ll want more than one.\n5 oz (141g), 266 yd\n(243m) skeins.\nSHOP KIT\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: www.redheart.com and www.crochettoday.com\n©2012 Coats & Clark\nRHC0107-021597M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 CONVERTIBLE CAPE | CROCHET 1 of 1"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "51 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "48",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "122 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Cape",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "30",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "27",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Pinkberry A.\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "RED HEART®",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Panel",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "25mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Panels",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Panel A 7",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "18 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "E300",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "198",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "364 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "333",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Convertible Cape",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "141",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "244 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "223",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "141",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "260",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "238",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Two",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Buy Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "more than one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "141",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "266 yd\n",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "243",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2012",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\nRHC0107-021597M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}