{
    "title": "Directions are for size 6-12 months; Next round (2 rounds): Repeat round",
    "steps": [
        "Directions are for size 6-12 months; Next round (2 rounds): Repeat round\nchanges for size 18-24 months are in 2—72 (78) sts.\nparentheses. Next 11 (16) rounds: Ch 2, dc in each dc\naround, join with slip st in beg dc.\nCircumference at top: 20” (51 cm) Last round (edging): Ch 1, sc in first dc, *\nCircumference at bottom: 24 (26)” skip 2 dc, 5 dc in next dc, skip 2 dc, sc in\n(61 (66) cm) next dc; repeat from * to end of round, join\nLength: 7 (10)” (18 (25.5) cm) with a slip st in first sc.\nCROCHET\nFasten off.\nSKILL LEVEL\nINTERMEDIATE NOTES\nPoncho is worked from the top down in FLOWER EMBELLISHMENTS\njoined rounds with the right side always Choose points in the poncho where you\nfacing. want to add a flower. Join yarn with a slip\nAll stitches are worked through the back st around the post of the dc where the\nloop and the third loop (the strand below rightmost petal will be, (ch 3, 3 dc, ch 3, slip\nthe back loop, also known as Camel stitch). st) around that same post, turn work 90\nTo change color, work last stitch of old color degrees, (slip st, ch 3, 3 dc, ch 3, slip st) in\nWhat you will need:\nto last yarn over. Yarn over with new color space between dc sts on row above, turn\nand draw through all loops on hook to work 90 degrees, (slip st, ch 3, 3 dc, ch 3, slip\nRED HEART® Baby Hugs™\nMedium: 1 ball each 4830 Pool complete stitch. Proceed with new color. st) around post of next dc, turn work 90\nA, 4001 Frosting B, and 4410 degrees (slip st, ch 3, 3 dc, ch 3, slip st) in\nDolphin C Color Sequence space between dc sts on row below.\n3 (4) rounds with A Fasten off.\nSusan Bates® Crochet Hook:\n2 (3) rounds with B\n5.5mm [US I-9]\n1 round with C FINISHING\nSusan Bates® Split lock stitch 2 (3) rounds with B Weave in all loose ends.\nmarkers 1 round with A\n2 (3) rounds with B ABBREVIATIONS\nYarn needle\n3 (5) rounds with C A, B, C = Color A, Color B, Color C etc; ch =\nGAUGE: 12 dc = 4” (10 cm); 1 round (edging) with A chain; dc = double crochet; dec = decrease;\n8½ dc rows = 4” (10 cm) when inc = increase; sc = single crochet; st(s) =\nworked in Camel stitch (see Baby’s First PONCHO stitch(es); * or ** = repeat whatever follows\nNotes). CHECK YOUR GAUGE.\nWith A, ch 60, join with a slip st to the first the * or ** as indicated.\nUse any size hook to obtain\nthe gauge. Poncho ch to work in the round.\nChange colors as you work following the See next page for flower chart and alternate photo\nRED HEART® Baby Color Sequence above.\nHugs™ Medium, Art Embellished with sweet flowers, this shoulder- Round 1: Ch 2 (does not count as a st), dc\nE404 Oeko-Tex Certified\nwarming poncho is the perfect accessory for in each ch around, join with slip st in beg dc.\n100% Acrylic baby yarn available\nRound 2 (inc round): Place 6 markers\nin 4.5 oz (127 g) 247 yds a stylish baby. Using new Baby Hugs yarn\n(225 m) balls evenly spaced around previous round, ch 2, *\nmeans that you have the assurance that your\ndc in each dc to marked st, 2 dc in marked\nhandmades are made with quality yarn. st, remove marker; repeat from * 5 more\ntimes, dc in each dc to end of round, join\nSHOP KIT\nwith slip st in beg dc – 66 sts.\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: redheart.com\n©RH 20C 10 62 C0 o7 a- t0 s1 &7 2 C9 la2 rkM | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 BABY’S FIRST PONCHO | CROCHPEaTg e 1 1 o off 22\nstart\nhere\nSymbol Key:\nSlip st\nCh\nDc\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: redheart.com\n©R2H01C60 C2o0a7t-s0 &1 7C2la9r2kM | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 BABY’S FIRST PONCHO | CROCHP Ea Tge 22 oof f 2 2"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "6-12 months",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18-24 months",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2—72",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "78",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Next 11",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st in beg dc",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "51 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "26",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "61",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "66",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "25.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Poncho",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "Choose",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "third",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Camel",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "90",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st, ch",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "90 degrees",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st, ch",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4830",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "90",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4001",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4410 degrees",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st, ch",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Dolphin C Color Sequence",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5.5mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "C FINISHING\n",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "B Weave",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "C A",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "=",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Camel",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Baby’s",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Notes",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art Embellished",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Round 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "Oeko-Tex Certified",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st in beg dc",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "100%",
            "label": "PERCENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "Round 2 (inc round",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "127",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "247",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Baby Hugs",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "225",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "66",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "C0",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "FIRST",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Symbol Key",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "FIRST",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2 2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}