{
    "title": "CROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER",
    "steps": [
        "CROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nTHE CAPELET | CROCHET SHOP KIT\nNOTE: Work with one strand each of CA and CB held\ntogether as one throughout.\nBeg at neck edge, ch 96 (108); join with a sl st in first ch to\nform a ring, taking care that ch is not twisted.\nRnd 1: Ch 1, sc in same ch as joining, * skip next 2 ch; 5\ndc in next ch – shell made; skip next 2 ch **, sc in next ch;\nrep from * around, end at **; join with a sl st in first sc – 16\n(18)shells.\nRnd 2: Ch 5, * skip 2 dc, sc in next dc, ch 2, skip next 2 dc\n**, dc in sc, ch 2; rep from * around, end at **; join in 3rd\nch of ch-5.\nRnd 3: Ch 1, sc in same st as joining, shell in next sc, * sc\nin next dc, shell in next sc; rep from * around; join.\nRnds 4 and 5: Rep Rnds 2 and 3.\nRnd 6: Ch 6, * skip 2 dc, sc in next dc, ch 3, skip next 2 dc\n**, dc in sc, ch 3; rep from * around, end at **; join in 3rd\nch of ch-6.\nRnd 7: Ch 1, sc in same st as joining, ch 1, shell in next\nsc, ch 1, * sc in dc, ch 1, shell in sc, ch 1; rep from *\naround; join.\nRnds 8-15: Rep Rnds 6 and 7 four more times.\nRnd 16: Ch 7, * skip 2 dc, sc in next dc, ch 4, skip next 2\ndc **, dc in sc, ch 4; rep from * around, end at **; join in\n3rd ch of ch-7.\nThe Capelet\nRnd 17: Ch 1, sc in same st as joining, ch 2, shell in\nnext sc, ch 2, * sc in dc, ch 2, shell in sc, ch 2; rep from *\naround; join.\nRnds 18-21: Rep Rnds 16 and 17 twice more. Fasten off.\nDesigned by Marilyn Coleman.\nNeck Edging: With right side facing, attach yarn at center\nback neck; ch 1, sc in same st as joining, sc in sp, * sc in\nCapelet directions are for Size Small/Medium; changes\nnext st, sc in sp; rep from * around; join – 64 (72) sc.\nfor Size Large/Extra Large are in parentheses.\nRnd 2: Ch 4, skip first 2 sc, * dc in next sc, ch 1, skip next\nsc; rep from * around; join to 3rd ch of ch-4.\nRED HEART® “Super Saver®”: 1 (2) skeins each 313\nRnd 3: Ch 1, sc in same st as joining, sc in sp, * sc in dc,\nAran CA and 305 Aspen Print CB\nsc in sp; rep from * around; join. Fasten off.Weave in ends.\nTie: Make a chain 60 (70)” long. Fasten off. Beg at center\nCrochet Hook: 8mm [US L-11].\nfront, weave chain through the ch-1 sps of Edging Rnd 2.\nYarn needle.\nMake two 1½” diameter pom poms and attach one at each\nend of tie.\nGAUGES: 12 sts = 4½” in pat Rows 1-5; 20 sts = 7½” in\npat Rows 16-21; 5 rnds = 4”; 8 sts = 4” in sc with double\nstrand of yarn. CHECK YOUR GAUGE. Use any size\nRED HEART® “Super Saver®”,\nhook to obtain the gauges.\nArt. E300, 7 oz, 364 yds\nUpper Circumference (Finished): 32 (36)”.\nLower Circumference: 60 (68)”.\nABBREVIATIONS: beg = beginning; CA, CB = Colors\nLength: 17½”.\nA, B; ch = chain; dc = double crochet; mm = millimeters;\npat = pattern; rep = repeat; rnd(s) = round(s); sc = single\ncrochet; sl = slip; sps = spaces; st(s) = stitch(es);\n* or ** = repeat whatever follows the * or ** as indicated.\nFor more ideas & inspiration —\n©2009 Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box 12229 www.redheart.com www.coatsandclark.com\nRHC0107-023762M G| LrAeeSnTv UilPleD, ASTCE D29: A61U2G-U02S2T9 2 019 www.crochettoday.com www.knitandcrToHcEh CeAtPtoELdEaT y| C.cRoOmCHET 1 of 1"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CAPELET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Beg",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "96",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "108",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 1: Ch 1",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnds 4",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7 four",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18-21",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Marilyn Coleman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Capelet",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size Small/Medium",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "64",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "72",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size Large/Extra Large",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "313",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Aran CA",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "305 Aspen Print CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "70",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Beg",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "US L-11",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Edging Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "two 1½",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "16-21",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RED HEART®",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "364",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Upper Circumference (Finished",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "32",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "36",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Lower Circumference",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "60",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "17½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2009",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2 019",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CeAtPtoELdEaT y| C.cRoOmCHET 1 of 1\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        }
    ]
}