{
    "title": "Poncho measures 66” circumference x 15” FINISHING",
    "steps": [
        "Poncho measures 66” circumference x 15” FINISHING\nlong (167.5 x 38 cm). Sew shoulders to back.\nSpecial Stitch Neck Edging\ndc2tog = [Yarn over, insert hook in next Round 1 (right side): With right side\nstitch, yarn over and pull up loop, yarn over, of back facing, join yarn with sc at right\ndraw through 2 loops] 2 times, yarn over, shoulder seam, sc evenly around neck edge;\ndraw through all 3 loops on hook. join with slip st in first sc.\nCROCHET\nSKILL LEVEL Round 2: Ch 1, sc in each sc around; join\nEASY Special Technique with slip st in first sc. Fasten off.\nJoin with sc = Place a slip knot on hook,\nDesigned by Michele Maks insert hook in indicated stitch, yarn over Bottom Edging\nand pull up a loop, yarn over and draw Row 1 (right side): With right side of front\nthrough both loops on hook. facing and working in opposite side of\nWhat you will need: foundation ch, join yarn with sc in first ch, sc\nPONCHO in each ch across, turn—83 sc.\nRED HEART® Tweed Twist™:\nBack Row 2: Ch 1, sc in each sc across. Fasten off.\n3 balls 9312 Neon Mix\nCh 85. Repeat bottom edging across back.\nSusan Bates® Crochet Hook: Row 1 (right side): Dc in 4th ch from hook\n8mm [US L-11] (beginning ch count as first dc) and in each Side Edging\nch across, turn—83 dc. Row 1 (right side): With right side of front\nYarn needle\nRows 2–22: Ch 3 (counts as first dc here bottom edging facing and working in ends\nand throughout), dc in each st across to of rows, join yarn with sc in Row 2, sc in\nGAUGE: 10 sts = 4” (10 cm); 6\nrows = 4” (10 cm). CHECK YOUR beginning ch, dc in top of beginning ch, each row across front and back edges, turn.\nGAUGE. Use any size hook to turn—21 dc. Fasten off. Row 2: Ch 1, sc in each sc across. Fasten off.\nobtain the gauge. With right side of back bottom edging\nFront facing, repeat side edging across back and\nRows 1–20: Work same as back. front of other side.\nWith side edges of front and back held\nRED HEART® Tweed First Shoulder together, sew 6” (15 cm) from bottom\nTwist™, Art E836 Row 1 (right side): Ch 3, dc in next 29 dc; edge on each side of poncho to create arm\navailable in 3.5 oz Set the Trend leave remaining sts unworked, turn—30 dc. openings.\n(100 g) 179 yd (163 m)\nRow 2: Ch 3, dc2tog, dc in remaining sts to Weave in loose ends.\nballs\nPoncho beginning ch, dc in top of beginning ch—29 Continued...\ndc.Fasten off.\nInstead of a boring cardigan or jacket wear this 2nd Shoulder\nnew crochet poncho style and look oh-so stylish! Row 1 (right side): With right side facing,\nskip next 23 dc, join yarn with slip st in next\nIt looks great on all ages, as you can see in the\ndc, ch 3, dc in remaining dc—30 dc.\nphoto on next page.\nRow 2: Repeat Row 2 of first shoulder.\nSHOP KIT\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: redheart.com\n©RH 20C 10 61 C0 o7 a- t0 s1 &7 9 C2 la2 rkM | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 SET THE TREND PONCHO | CROCHPEaTge 11 ooff 22\nABBREVIATIONS\nch = chain(s); dc = double crochet;\nsc = single crochet; st(s) = stitch(es).\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: redheart.com\n©R 2H 01C 60 C1 o0 a7 t- s0 &1 7 C9 la2 r2 kM | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 SET THE TREND PONCHO | CROCHPEaTge 22 ooff 22"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "Poncho",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "66",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "167.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "38 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Michele Maks",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Bottom Edging",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "US L-11",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Twist",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art E836 Row",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 29",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Set the Trend",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "turn—30",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "100",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "179 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "163",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Poncho",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "this 2nd",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 23",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip st",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "C0",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "TREND",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "60 C1",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "TREND",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "22",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}