{
    "title": "Poncho",
    "steps": [
        "Poncho\nRow 6:With CB, rep Row 2.\nLW1460 Intermediate Row 7:With C A, rep Row 3.\nRep Rows 4-7 two (three) more times. Fasten\nDesigned by Mary Jane Protus.\noff. Piece should measure approximately 231/ 2\" x\nDirections are for size Small (2-3 101/ 2(13)\".\nyears); changes for size Large (4-6\nyears) are in parentheses. FINISHING: Sew short side of first piece to\nlong edge of second piece following diagram.\nRED HEART® “Baby Clouds™”, Art. E710\nThen sew short side of second piece to long\n(6 ounce/140 yard solid; 4.5 ounce/105 yard\nedge of first piece.\nmulti skein): 6 Ounces No. 9311 Cloud C A, 4.5\nounces No. 9351 Tutti-Frutti CB, and 3.5\nounces No. 9322 Creamsicle CC. Lower Edging-Rnd 1:With right side facing,\nattach CCin a corner; ch 1, * (sc, ch 1, sc) all in\nCrochet Hook:10mm [US N-15]. corner, work sc evenly to next corner; rep from\nYarn needle. * around; join with a sl st in first sc. Fasten off.\nRnd 2:With right side facing, attach C Ain ch-\nGAUGE: 7 sts = 4\"; Rows 1-7 = 5\" in pat.\n1 sp at corner; ch 1, ** (sc, ch 3, sc) all in cor-\nCHECK YOUR GAUGE. Use any size\nner, ch 3, skip next sc, * sc in next sc, ch 3, skip\nhook to obtain the gauge.\nnext sc; rep from * to next corner ch-1 sp; rep\nfrom ** around; join. Fasten off.\nTo Change Color in Sc: Work to one st\nbefore required color change, draw up a lp in\nNeck Edging: With right side facing, attach\nnext st, drop color in use; with next color to be\nCCat shoulder area; ch 1, sc evenly around neck\nused yo and draw through 2 lps on hook.\nworking a decrease over each seam area (to\nTo Change Color in Dc: Work to one st decrease: draw up a lp on each side of the seam,\nbefore required color change, yo and draw up a yo and draw through all 3 lps on hook); join to\nlp in next st, yo and draw through 2 lps, drop first sc. Fasten off.\ncolor in use; with next color to be used yo and\nTie:With C A, ch 100 (120). Fasten off. Weave\ndraw through 2 lps on hook.\nthrough sc of Neck Edging. Make a knot at each\nend of tie.\nPONCHO (Make 2 pieces alike):With C A,\nch 42.\nABBREVIATIONS: ch = chain; dc = double\nRow 1 (Right Side):Sc in 2nd ch from hook crochet; hdc = half double crochet; lp(s) =\nloop (s); m m= millimeters; rep= repeat; rnd\nand in each ch across changing to CBin last st;\n= round; sc= single crochet; sl st= slip stitch;\nturn – 41 sc.\nsp(s) = space (s); st(s) = stitch (es); yo =\nyarn over; *or **= repeat whatever follows the\nRow 2: With CB, ch 3, skip first sc; [yo and\n* or ** as indicated; [] = work directions in\ndraw up a lp] 3 times all in next sc, yo and draw\nbrackets the number of times specified.\nthrough 6 lps, yo and draw through 2 lps– puff\nstmade; * ch 1, skip next sc, puff st in next sc;\nrep from * to last sc; dc in last sc changing to\nC A; turn.\nRow 3:With C A, ch 1, sc in dc, sc in puff st, *\nsc in ch-1 sp, sc in puff st; rep from * to last st;\nsc in top of ch-3 changing to CC; turn.\nRow 4:With CC, ch 2, skip first sc, hdc in next\nsc and in each sc across changing to C Ain last\nsc; turn.\nRow 5: With C A, ch 1, sc in each hdc across\nand in top of ch-2 changing to CB in last sc;\nturn.\n©2005 COATS & CLARK, P.O. Box 12229, Greenville, SC,\n29612-0229\nwww.coatsandclark.com Printed in USA 0405"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "two",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "three",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Mary Jane Protus",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "approximately 231/ 2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Small",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2-3 101/ 2(13",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4-6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "second",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Baby Clouds",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "second",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "multi skein",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "6 Ounces",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "4.5\nounces",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Tutti-Frutti CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3.5\nounces",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Creamsicle CC",
            "label": "EVENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "CCin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "C Ain",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "100",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "120",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "C A",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "42",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CBin",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "C Ain",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2005",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "COATS & CLARK",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "P.O. Box 12229",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "www.coatsandclark.com Printed",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}