{
    "title": "One size fits most. Rows 3-4: Ch 3, turn, dc in next dc, *ch 7, dc",
    "steps": [
        "One size fits most. Rows 3-4: Ch 3, turn, dc in next dc, *ch 7, dc\nCapelet measures 10” (25 cm) x 48” in next dc, ch 7, dc in next 2 dc; repeat from\n122 cm). *to end.\nFlowers measure 5” (13 cm) across. Row 5: Ch 3, turn, dc in next dc, *ch 3, dc in\ncenter ch of ch-7 space, ch 3, dc in next dc,\nFLOWERS ch 3, dc in center ch of ch-7 space, ch 3, dc in\n(Make 4 with A and 4 with B) next 2 dc; repeat from * to end.\nCh 4, slip st in first ch to form ring. Row 6: Ch 3, dc in next dc, *3 dc in ch-3\nCROCHET\nRound 1: Ch 2 (counts as hdc here and space, dc in next dc, 3 dc in ch-3 space, dc in\nSKILL LEVEL\nthroughout), work 8 hdc in ring, slip st in top of next 2 dc; repeat from * to end.\nEASY\nbeginning ch – 9 hdc. Fasten off.\nDesigned by Double Stitch Twins. Round 2: Ch 3 (counts as dc here and Row 7: With right side facing, join A in 30th\nthroughout), dc in same st, 2 dc in each hdc st from edge, ch 3, dc in next 61 dc, leave\naround, slip st in top of beginning ch – 18 dc. remaining sts unworked – 62 dc.\nWhat you will need:\nRound 3: *Ch 4, slip st in next 2 dc, slip st in Ruffle Row 8: Ch 3, turn, [3 dc in next dc] 30\nnext dc, repeat from * around, slip st in first Continued...\nRED HEART® Super Saver\nst – 6 ch-4 spaces.\nChunky®: 1 skein each 776 Dark\nRound 4: (Sc, hdc, 3 dc, hdc, sc) in each ch-4\nOrchid A and 905 Magenta B.\nspace around for petals, slip st in beginning\nSusan Bates® Crochet Hook: sc – 6 petals.\n9mm [US M-13]. Fasten off.\nDecorative hook and eye closure,\nNeck Piece\nyarn needle.\nJoining Flowers\nGAUGE: Gauge is not critical for With right side facing, join B in center dc on\nthis project. one petal of first B Flower, ch 3, slip st in\ncenter dc of one petal of next A flower.\nBuy Yarn Fasten off.\nJoin B in center dc on corresponding petal\nRED HEART® Super on opposite side of A Flower, ch 3, slip st in\nSaver® Chunky®, center dc of one petal on next B Flower.\nArt. E778, available in Romantic Flower\nAlternating colors, repeat to join 8 Flowers.\nsolid color 6oz (170g),\n207 yd (189m) skeins.\nCapelet CAPELET\nRow 1: With right side facing, join B in\nbetween sc between petals along unjoined\nJewel tones provide the drama and the design\nlong side of A Flower, ch 3, dc in same st,\nprovides the romance. Flowers and lace *ch 15, 2 dc in corresponding space on next\ncombine for a unique wrap to set off Flower; repeat from * to end.\nRow 2: Ch 3, turn, dc in next dc, *ch 7, dc in\nyour favorite look.\ncenter ch of ch-15 space, ch 7, dc in next 2\ndc; repeat from * across, tto end.\nSHOP KIT\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: www.redheart.com and www.crochettoday.com\n©2012 Coats & Clark\nRHC0107-021517M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 ROMANTIC FLOWER CAPELET | CROCHET 1 of 2\nLW3001 Romatic Flower Capelet\ntimes, change to B, [3 dc in next dc] 30 times.\nFasten off.\nFINISHING\nSew hook on 3rd Flower and eye on 6th\nFlower.\nWeave in ends.\nAbbreviations: A, B, C = Color A, B, C;\nch = chain; dc = double crochet; mm =\nmillimeters; sc = single crochet; st(s) =\nstitch(es); [ ] = work directions in brackets the\nnumber of times specified; * or ** = repeat\nwhatever follows the * or ** as indicated.\nRHC0107-021517M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 1, 2019 ROMANTIC FLOWER CAPELET | CROCHET 2 of 2\nRedHeart.com\nFind more ideas & inspiration: www.redheart.com and www.crochettoday.com\n©2012 Coats & Clark"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Capelet",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "25 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "48",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "122 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "SKILL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "30th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 61",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "62 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ruffle",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "30",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Chunky®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "776 Dark\nRound 4",
            "label": "MONEY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sc",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "905",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Magenta B.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "US M-13",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck Piece",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Gauge",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first B Flower",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RED HEART® Super",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Chunky®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "B Flower",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Romantic Flower\nAlternating",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "170",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "207 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "189",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Capelet CAPELET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Jewel",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch-15",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2012",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\nRHC0107-021517M",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "30",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd Flower",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "6th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "=",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 1, 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2012",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\n",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}