{
    "title": "Join on 1 Side:Work Rnds 1-4 as given above.",
    "steps": [
        "Join on 1 Side:Work Rnds 1-4 as given above.\nGranny Poncho\nJoining Rnd 5:Sl st in next dc and next 2 ch;ch 1,sc\nin same sp,ch 3,arch,ch 3,sc in next sp,ch 3,* (3 tr,\nLW1456 Intermediate ch 2,sl st in corner ch-5 sp of completed motif,ch 2,3\ntr) all in next ch-5 sp *,ch 1,sl st in next ch-3 sp of\nDesigned by Gayle Bunn. completed motif,ch 1,sc in next ch-5 sp,ch 1,sl st in\nnext ch-3 sp of completed motif,ch 1,arch,sl st in\nOne size fits most women. arch of completed motif,ch 1,sl st in next ch-3 sp of\ncompleted motif,ch 1,sc in next ch-5 sp,ch 1,sl st in\nRED HEART® “LusterSheen®”, Art. E721 (4 next ch-3 sp of completed motif,ch 1,rep from * to *\nounce/335 yard skein):4Color Poncho:3Skeins No. once – one side joined;complete rnd.Fasten off.\n0002 Black CA and 1 skein each No.0805 Natural CB,\nJoin on 2 Sides:Work as for Joining Rnd 5 across first\nNo.0824 Med.Blue CCand No.0735 Hot Pink CD.\nside,joining at next corner by working the sl st into the\n1Color Poncho:4Skeins No.0824 Med.Blue.\nsl st of previous joining,join 2nd side;complete rnd.\nCrochet Hook:3.5mm [US E-4].Yarn needle.\nFINISHING: Join short side of First Piece to long\nedge of 2nd Piece as follows:with right sides together\nGAUGE:One Motif = 41/2\"x41/2\".CHECK YOUR and working through both layers,joinCAin corner\nGAUGE.Use any size hook to obtain the gauge. sps at lower edge;ch 1,sc in same sp,* ch 5,sc in next\nch-3 sp,ch 5,skip next ch-3 sp,sc in next arch,ch 5,\nNOTE: AFTER THE FIRST MOTIF ALL OTH- skip next ch-3 sp,sc in next ch-3 sp,ch 5,sc in joining\nERS ARE JOINED WHILE WORKING RND 5. st;rep from * across.Fasten off.\nJoin short side of 2nd Piece to long edge of First\n4COLOR PONCHO:MOTIF 1 (2,3,4):With CC Piece in same manner.\n(CD,CB,CC),ch 4;join with a sl st in first ch to form\naring. Lower Edging: With right side facing, join CA at\nRnd 1:Ch 4,[dc,ch 1] 11 times in ring;join with a sl seam of lower edge;ch 1;(sc,ch 3,2 dc) all in same st\nst in 3rd ch of ch-4.Fasten off. –gr (group)made;* skip next tr,gr in next tr,[gr in\nRnd 2:Join CB(CC,CD,CD)in any sp;ch 3;[yo and next ch-3 sp] 4 times,skip next tr,gr in next tr **,gr\ndraw up a lp,yo and draw through 2 lps] twice all in in joining st;rep from * around,working gr in ch-5\nsame sp,yo and draw through all 3 lps on hook–beg sps of points,end at **;join.Fasten off.\nclustermade;* ch 3;[yo and draw up a lp,yo and draw\nthrough 2 lps] 3 times all in next sp,yo and draw Neck Edging-Rnd 1:With right side facing,join CA\nthrough all 4 lps on hook–cl (cluster)made;rep from at joining between 2 motifs at left shoulder;ch 1,sc in\n*around;ch 3;join to top of beg cluster.Fasten off. same st,*ch 3,skip next tr,sc in next tr,[ch 3,sc in\nRnd 3:Join CD(CB,CC,CB)in any sp;ch 1,(sc,ch next ch-3 sp] 4 times,ch 3,skip next tr,sc in next tr **,\n3,sc) all in same sp,* ch 5,(sc,ch 3,sc) all in next sp; ch 3,sc in next joining;rep from * to “V”of front;rep\nrep from * around;ch 2,dc in first sc to join and form from * to “V”of back;rep from * to end of rnd,end\nlast ch-5 sp.Fasten off. at **;ch 1,dc in first sc.\nRnd 4:Join CAin any ch-5 sp;ch 3,(dc,ch 5,2dc) all Rnds 2-4:[* Ch 3,sc in next sp;rep from * to “V”;sl\nin same sp,* (2 dc,ch 5,2 dc) all in next ch-5 sp;rep st in next sp] twice;** ch 3,sc in next sp;rep from **\nfrom * around;join to top of ch-3. to dc;ch 1,dc in dc.Fasten off at end of Rnd 4.\nRnd 5:Sl st in next dc and next 2 ch;ch 1,sc in same\nsp,* ch 3;yo and draw up a lp in next dc,yo and draw 1COLOR PONCHO-Make2Pieces Alike:Join 8\nthrough 2 lps,skip next 2 dc,yo and draw up a lp in motifs into 4 strips,omitting all reference to color\nnext dc, yo and draw through 2 lps, yo and draw changes and changing beg of rnds as follows:Rnds 2\nthrough all 3 lps on hook–archmade;ch 3,sc in next and 3:Sl st in next sp.Rnd 4:Ch 3,(dc,ch 5,2 dc) all\nsp,ch 3,(3 tr,ch 5,3 tr) all in next sp for corner,ch 3 over dc.\n**,sc in next sp;rep from * around,end at **;join in\nfirst sc.Fasten off.\nABBREVIATIONS:beg=beginning;ch=chain;dc=double\nFIRST PIECE:Join 8 motifs into 4 strips as follows: crochet;lp(s)=loop (s);mm=millimeters;rep=repeat;rnd=\nFirst Strip:[Motif 1,Motif 2,Motif 3,Motif 4] twice. round;sc=single crochet;sl st=slip stitch;sp(s)=space (s);\n2nd Strip:[Motif 2,Motif 3,Motif 4,Motif 1] twice. st(s)=stitch (es);yo=yarn over;*or **=repeat whatever fol-\n3rd Strip:[Motif 3,Motif 4,Motif 1,Motif 2] twice. lows the * or ** as indicated;[]=work directions in brackets the\nnumber of times specified.\n4th Strip:[Motif 4,Motif 1,Motif 2,Motif 3] twice.\n2ND PIECE:Join 8 motifs into 4 strips as follows:\nFirst Strip:[Motif 3,Motif 4,Motif 1,Motif 2] twice.\n2nd Strip:[Motif 1,Motif 2,Motif 3,Motif 4] twice.\n3rd Strip:[Motif 2,Motif 3,Motif 4,Motif 1] twice.\n4th Strip:[Motif 4,Motif 1,Motif 2,Motif 3] twice.\n©2005 COATS & CLARK,P.O.Box 12229,Greenville,SC,29612-0229\nwww.coatsandclark.com Printed in USA 0305"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2,3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Gayle Bunn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "LusterSheen®",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,rep",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "joined;complete rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "0002",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Black CA",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "No.0805 Natural CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "No.0824 Med",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "First Piece",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "41/2\"x41/2\"",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "joinCAin",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "FIRST",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "ERS ARE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "RND 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "First",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CC Piece",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4;join",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 1:Ch 4,[dc,ch 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ring;join",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck Edging-Rnd 1",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "CA",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "between 2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3;join",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next tr,[ch 3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 3:Join CD(CB,CC",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,(sc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5,(sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2,dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 4",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5,2dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,dc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 4",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 5:Sl st in",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3;yo",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "PONCHO-Make2Pieces",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3,sc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5,3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "FIRST",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "First Strip:[Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,Motif",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "stitch;sp(s)=space (s)",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd Strip:[Motif 2,Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd Strip:[Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th Strip:[Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,Motif",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2ND",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "First Strip:[Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd Strip:[Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,Motif",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd Strip:[Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2,Motif",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th Strip:[Motif",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1,Motif",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2005",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "COATS & CLARK",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12229,Greenville",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "www.coatsandclark.com Printed",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "USA",
            "label": "GPE"
        }
    ]
}