{
    "title": "GAUGE: 11 dc = 4”; 8 rows = 4”. CHECK YOUR",
    "steps": [
        "GAUGE: 11 dc = 4”; 8 rows = 4”. CHECK YOUR\nGAUGE. Use any size hook to obtain the gauge.\nCAPELET\nCh 46.\nRow 1: Hdc in 2nd ch from hook and each ch.\nRows 2-3: Ch 2 (counts as hdc here and throughout),\nturn, hdc in each hdc across across – 45 sts.\nRow 4: Ch 3 (counts as dc here and throughout), turn,\n2 dc in next hdc, [ch 1, skip next hdc, 2 dc in next hdc]\nacross to last st, dc in last st.\nRow 5: Ch 3, turn, dc in each dc and ch-1 space across\n– 67 dc.\nRow 6: Ch 3, turn, dc in each dc across.\nRow 7: Ch 3, turn, dc in next 4 dc, 2 dc in next dc, [dc\nin next 5 dc, 2 dc in next dc] across to last st, dc in last\nst – 78 dc.\nMini Capelet\nRow 8: Ch 4 (counts as tr here and throughout), turn, tr\nTake an ordinary dress or tee to outright charming\nin next 4 dc, 2 tr in next dc, [tr in next 5 dc, 2 tr in next\nwith this capelet that can be crocheted in little time.\ndc] across – 91 tr.\nWear it whatever the season for a chic accessory\nthat isn’t your usual necklace or scarf.\nRow 9: Ch 4, turn, tr in next 2 tr, [ch 2, skip next tr, tr in\nnext 3 tr] across.\nLW2862\nRow 10: Ch 12 (counts as tr and ch 8), turn, 2 tr in next\nch-2 space, [ch 8, 2 tr in next ch-2 space] across to last\nDesigned by Double Stitch Twins. 3 tr, tr in last 3 tr.\nOne size fits most. Row 11: Ch 4, turn, tr in next 2 tr, [8 tr in next ch-8\nspace, tr in next 2 tr] across to last ch-8 space, 8 tr in\nCapelet measures 7” long. last ch-8 space. Fasten off.\nRED HEART® Shimmer™: 1 Ball 1536 Purple. FINISHING\nEdging and Ties\nCrochet Hook: 5mm [US H-8]. Ch 50, with right side facing, join yarn opposite\nYarn needle. foundation ch, sc in each ch across, ch 50.\nFasten off. Weave in ends.\nFor Susan Bates® knitting needles & crochet hooks - www.shopredheart.com\nFor more ideas & inspiration - www.redheart.com www.crochettoday.com www.yourknittinglife.com ©2012 Coats & Clark\nRED HEART® Shimmer™ Art. E763\navailable in 3.5 oz (100 g), 280 yd (256 m)\nballs.\nAbbREvIATIONS: ch = chain; dc = double crochet;\nhdc = half double crochet; mm = millimeters; sc =\nsingle crochet; st(s) = stitch(es); tr = triple or treble\ncrochet; [ ] = work directions in brackets the number of\ntimes specified.\nFor Susan Bates® knitting needles & crochet hooks - www.shopredheart.com\nFor more ideas & inspiration - www.redheart.com www.crochettoday.com www.yourknittinglife.com ©2012 Coats & Clark"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "46",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "45",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "67",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 4",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 5",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Mini Capelet",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 4",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 5",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "91",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Wear",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8)",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "last 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Capelet",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Edging and Ties\nCrochet Hook",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "50",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "50",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "needles & crochet",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2012",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\nRED HEART® Shimmer",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "100",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "280 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "256",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "needles & crochet",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2012",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\n",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}