{
    "title": "SB708-004 Crochet Short Poncho",
    "steps": [
        "SB708-004 Crochet Short Poncho\nPoncho fits most women.\nRED HEART® \"Light & Lofty®\": 12 Ounces No. 9617\nPheasant.\nCrochet Hook: 11.5mm [US P-16].\nYarn needle.\nGAUGE: 7 sts = 4\"; 8 rows = 7\" in pattern. CHECK YOUR\nGAUGE. Use any size hook to obtain the gauge.\nCh 25.\nRow 1 (Right Side): Sc in 2nd ch from hook and each ch\nacross; turn – 24 sc.\nRow 2: Ch 3, skip first sc, * skip next sc, dc in next sc, dc in\nskipped sc (this dc encloses the last dc made); rep from * to\nlast sc; dc in last sc; turn.\nRow 3: Ch 1, sc in each dc across and in top of ch-3; turn.\nRep Rows 2 and 3 until 48\" from beginning, end by working\nRow 3. Fasten off.\nFINISHING: Sew the short (beginning) edge to the last 14\"\nof left hand side of the long edge.\nNeck/Outside Edging: With right side facing, attach yarn at\nneck/outside edge; ch 1, work (sc, ch 1) evenly around\nneck/entire outside edge; join with a sl st to first sc. Fasten off.\nWeave in loose ends.\nDesigned by Michele Thompson.\nABBREVIATIONS: ch = chain; dc = double crochet; mm =\nmillimeters; rem = remaining; rep = repeat; sc = single crochet; * =\nrepeat whatever follows the * as indicated.\n©2007 Coats & Clark, P.O. Box 12229, Greenville, SC, 29612-0229\nGo to www.coatsandclark.com for FREE patterns."
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "Light & Lofty®",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "11.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "P-16",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yarn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "48",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck/Outside Edging:",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Michele Thompson",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2007",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "P.O. Box 12229",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "FREE",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}