{
    "title": "CROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY",
    "steps": [
        "CROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nCROCHET TOPPER | CROCHET SHOP KIT\nBACK: Ch 49 (55, 63).\nRow 1 (Right Side): Dc in 4th ch from hook and in each\nch across; turn – 47 (53, 61) sts.\nRow 2: Ch 1, skip first dc, dc in each dc across and in top\nof ch-3; turn.\nRep Row 2 until 12 (14, 16) rows in all have been worked.\nYoke: Ch 1, working in BACK LPS ONLY, sc in each dc\nacross and in top of ch-3; turn.\nNext Row: Ch 1, sc in BACK LP ONLY of each sc across;\nturn.\nRep last row 6 (7, 8) more times – 8 (9, 10) rows of sc\ncompleted. Fasten off.\nFRONT: Work same as back until 4 (5, 6) sc rows of yoke\nhave been completed.\nDivide for Neck/Shoulder: Keeping continuity of pattern,\nwork over first 17 (20, 24) sc; TURN. Work 3 more rows.\nFront should measure same as Back. Fasten off.\nSecond Shoulder: Skip center 13 sts of last long row,\nattach yarn and work across remaining 17 (20, 24) sc.\nComplete to correspond to first shoulder.\nTURTLENECK: Ch 14 (15, 16).\nRow 1 (Right Side): Sc in 2nd ch from hook and in each\nch across; turn – 13 (14, 15) sc.\nRow 2: Ch 1, sc in BACK LP ONLY of each sc across;\nturn.\nRows 3-40: Rep Row 2. Fasten off.\nCrochet Topper\nFINISHING: Sew shoulder seams. Sew beginning and end\nof Turtleneck together to form a tube. Sew to neck edge\nwith seam at center back.\nDesigned by Michele Thompson Outer Edging-Rnd 1: With right side facing, attach yarn\nat a shoulder seam; ch 1, work sc evenly around entire\nDirections are for size Small. Changes for Medium and outside edge, working 3 sc at corners; join with a sl st to\nLarge follow in parentheses. first sc.\nRnd 2: Ch 1, sc in BACK LPS ONLY of each sc around,\nRED HEART® “Light & Lofty®”: 4 (5, 5) skeins 9376 increasing at corners if necessary; join. Fasten off. Weave\nWine. in ends.\nCrochet Hook: 11.5mm [US P-16].\nYarn needle. RED HEART® “Light & Lofty®”,\nArt. E708, solids - 6 oz, 140 yds;\nGAUGE: 8 sts = 5”; 12 rows = 13” in dc. CHECK YOUR multis - 4.5 oz, 105 yds\nGAUGE. Use any size hook to obtain the gauge.\nTo fit Bust: 34 (38, 42)”. ABBREVIATIONS: ch = chain; dc = double crochet;\nFinished Width: 32 (35½, 40½)”. lp(s) = loop(s); mm = millimeters; rep = repeat;\nrnd = round; sc = single crochet; sl = slip; st(s) =\nstitch(es); * or ** = repeat whatever follows\nthe * or ** as indicated.\nFor more ideas & inspiration —\n©2009 Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box 12229 www.redheart.com www.coatsandclark.com\nGreenville, SC 29612-0229\nRHC0107-023663M | LAST UPDATED: AUGUST 2019 www.crochettoday.com www.knitanCdRcOrCoHcEhTe TtOtPoPdEaRy | .CcRoOmCHET 1 of 1"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "55",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "63",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "47",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "53, 61",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Yoke",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "BACK LPS",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "BACK LP",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8)",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "24",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "last long row",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "24",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Complete",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15,",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "15",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "BACK LP",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "3-40",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Michele Thompson",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rnd 2",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "BACK LPS",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Light & Lofty®",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9376",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "11.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "P-16",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "Light & Lofty®",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "140",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "105",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Bust",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "34",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "38",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "42",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Finished Width",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "32",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "35½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "40½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2009",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats & Clark\nP.O. Box",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "12229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "AUGUST 2019",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "TtOtPoPdEaRy",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}