{
    "title": "Medium36\"[91.5\"] WithB,work2rows.",
    "steps": [
        "Medium36\"[91.5\"] WithB,work2rows.\nLarge38\"[96.5\"] WithA,work6rows.\nExtra-Large40\"[101.5\"] WithB,work2rows.\nFinishedbust WithA,work4rows.\nExtra-Small34ins[86.5cm] WithB,work2rows.\nSmall36\"[91.5\"] WithA,work2rows.\nMedium38\"[96.5\"] WithB,work4rows.\nLarge40\"[101.5\"] WithA,work2rows.\nExtra-Large42\"[106.5\"] WithB,work6rows.\nWithA,work2rows.\nMATERIALS WithB,work8rows.\nWithA,work2rows.\nPatons®Grace(50g) WithB,work8rows.\nSizesXS(S-ML-XL) WithA,work2rows.\nMainColor(MC):(DarkBlue) These100rowsformStripePat.\n2(2-2-3-3balls)\nContrastA:(LightBlue)3(3-3-4-4)balls FRONT\nContrastB:(White)4(5-5-5-6)balls **WithMC,ch104(110-116-122-128).\nFoundation row: (RS). 1 sc in 2nd ch from\nSize4mm(U.S.Gor6)crochethookorsize hook.*Ch1.Missnextch.1scinnextch.Rep\nneededtoobtaintension. from*toendofch.Turn.103(109-115-121-\n127)sts.\nTENSION 1strow:Ch1.1scinfirstsc.*1scinnextch\n1sp.Ch1.Missnextsc.Repfrom*tolast\n24stsand23rows=4ins[10cm]inpat. 2sts.1scinnextch-1sp.1scinlastsc.Turn.\n(FirstrowofStripePatiscomplete)\nINSTRUCTIONS 2nd row: Ch 1. 1 sc in first sc. *Ch 1. Miss\nnextsc.1scinnextch-1sp.Repfrom*tolast\nThe instructions are written for smallest size. If sc.1scinlastsc.Turn.\nchangesarenecessaryforlargersizesthe Last2rowsformpat.\ninstructionswillbewrittenthus( ). First2rowsofStripePatarecompleted.\nStripePat Cont in pat, keeping cont of Stripe Pat until\nWithMC,work8rows. work from beg measures 2 ins [5 cm]. Place\nWithA,work2rows. firstsetofmarkersateachendoflastrow.\nWithMC,work6rows.\nPATONS® GRACE\nWithA,work2rows. ContinStripePatuntilworkfrombeg\nNAUTICAL TOP\nWithMC,work4rows. measures15(15-16-16-16½)ins[38(38-40.5-\n(TO CROCHET)\nWithA,work2rows. 40.5-42)cm],endingwithRSfacingfornext\nWithMC,work2rows. row.\nSIZES WithA,work4rows.\nWithMC,work2rows. Note:When100rowsofStripePatare\nBustmeasurement WithA,work6rows. complete,continpatwithBonly.\nExtra-Small32ins[81.5cm] WithMC,work2rows.\nSmall34\"[86.5\"] WithA,work8rows.\nABBREVIATIONS: www.patonsyarns.com/glossary\nArmholeshaping:1strow:Slstineachoffirst Nextrow:Ch1.Pattolast2sts.Sc2togover shaping.Patacross43(45-45-45-49)stsacross\n5sts.Ch1.Pattolast5sts.Turn.Leaveremsts last2sts.Turn. back neck edge. Work 31 (33-35-39-39) sc\nunworked.93(99-105-111-117)sts. Nextrow:Ch1.Sc2togoverfirst2sts. downleftsideofV-neckshapingtomarkedst.\n2ndrow:Workeveninpat. Turn. Turn.\n3rdrow:Ch1.Drawupaloopineachoffirst Pattolast2sts.Sc2togoverlast2sts.Turn. Proceedinpatas given forFrontuntilCollar\n2sts.Yohanddrawthroughall3loopsonhook– Nextrow:Ch1.Pattolast2sts.Sc2togover frombegmeasures3ins[7.5cm],endingwith\nSc2togmade.Pattolast2sts.Sc2togoverlast last2sts.Turn. RSfacingfornextrow.Fastenoff.\n2sts.Turn.** Rep last 2 rows 4 (5-3-1-1) time(s) more. 24\nReplast2rows3timesmore.85(91-97-103- (24-33-42-39)sts. CollarEdging:WithRSofCollarfacing,join\n109)sts. Bwithslstat1strowofCollar.Ch1.1scin\nSizesS,M,LandXLonly: samespaslastslst.13scupleftsideofCollar.\nV-neckshaping:Nextrow:(RS).Ch1.Sc2tog Nextrow:(RS).Ch1.Sc2togoverfirst2sts. 3scincorner.93(98-102-110-112)scacross\noverfirst2sts.Patacrossnext38(41-44-47- Pattoendofrow.Turn. longedgeofCollar.3scincorner.13scdown\n50)sts.Sc2togovernext2sts.Turn.Leaverem Nextrow:Ch1.Pattolast2sts.Sc2togover rightsideofCollar.JoinA.Turn.\nstsunworked.40(43-46-49-52)sts. last2sts.Turn. Nextrow:WithA,workinginbackloopsonly,\nNextrow:Ch1.Sc2togoverfirst2sts.Patto Rep last 2 rows (1-3-5-3) time(s) more. (20- 1scineachsctoendofrow,working3scin\nendofrow.Turn. 25-30-31)sts. corners.JoinB.Turn.\nNextrow:Ch1.Sc2togoverfirst2sts.Patto Nextrow:WithB,as2ndrow.Fastenoff.\nlast2sts.Sc2togoverlast2sts.Turn. All Sizes: Next row:(RS).Ch1.Sc2togover\nNextrow:Ch1.Sc2togoverfirst2sts.Patto first2sts.Pattoendofrow.Turn. SewsidesofCollarEdgingtoV-neckedge.Sew\nendofrow.Turn. Nextrow:Workeveninpat.Turn. sideseamsabovefirstsetofmarkers.\nReplast2rows4(5-3-1-1)timesmore.24(24- Replast2rows8(3-7-9-9)timesmore.15(16-\n33-42-39)sts. 17-20-21)sts.\nSizeSonly:WithB,work6rowseveninpat.\nSizesS,M,LandXLonly:\nNextrow:(RS).Ch1.Pattolast2sts.Sc2tog AllSizes:Fastenoff.\noverlast2sts.Turn.\nNextrow:Ch1.Pattoendofrow.Turn.Rep BACK\nlast2rows(1-3-5-3)time(s)more.(20-25-30- Workfrom**to**asgivenforFront.\n31)sts. Rep last 2 rows 9 (12-12-12-12) times more.\n73(73-79-85-91)sts. Front\nAllSizes:Nextrow:(RS).Ch1.Pattolast and\n2sts.Sc2togoverlast2sts.Turn. WithB,conteveninpatuntilarmhole Back\nNextrow:Workeveninpat.Turn. measures same length as Front to shoulders,\nReplast2rows8(3-7-9-9)timesmore.15(16- endingwithRSfacingfornextrow.Fastenoff.\n17-20-21)sts.\nFINISHING\nSizeSonly:WithB,work6rowseveninpat. Sewshoulderseams.Placesecondsetof\nmarkers¼inch[1cm]upalongleftandright\nAllSizes:Fastenoff. sidesofV-neckshapingfromV.\nWithRSofworkfacing,missnextst.Join COLLAR:WithRSofworkfacing,joinBat\nappropriate color with sl st to next st. Ch 1. markedstofrightsideofV-neckshapingwith\nSc2togoverfirst2sts.Pattolast2sts.Sc2tog slst.Ch1.1scinsamespaslastslst.Work30\noverlast2sts.Turn.38(41-44-47-50)sts. (32-34-38-38)scuprightsideofV-neck\n… a part of your life.\nP.O.Box40,ListowelON N4W3H3"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "Extra-Large40\"[101.5\"",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "Finishedbust WithA",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Extra",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "Extra-Large42\"[106.5",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "2(2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch104(110",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Turn.103(109-115-121-",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "127)sts",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1sp",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24stsand23rows=4ins[10cm]inpat. 2sts.1scinnextch-1sp.1scinlastsc",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "nextsc.1scinnextch-1sp",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Last2rowsformpat",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "StripePat Cont",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "pat",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Stripe Pat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "firstsetofmarkersateachendoflastrow",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRACE\nWithA",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "ContinStripePatuntilworkfrombeg",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "NAUTICAL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "measures15(15-16-16-16½)ins[38(38-40.5-",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "40.5-42)cm],endingwithRSfacingfornext",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Extra-Small32ins[81.5cm] WithMC",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "31",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "33",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "105",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2ndrow",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Workeveninpat",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rdrow",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Proceedinpatas",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fastenoff",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24-33-42-39)sts",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "109)sts",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3scincorner.93(98",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "102",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Patacrossnext38(41",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Leaverem Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "JoinA.Turn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Patto Rep",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20- 1scineachsctoendofrow",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "25-30-31)sts",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "JoinB.Turn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Patto Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "WithB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fastenoff",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Workeveninpat",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Replast2rows4(5-3-1-1)timesmore.24(24-",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "33",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "17-20-21)sts",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "WithB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fastenoff",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "31)sts",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Nextrow:(RS).Ch1.Pattolast",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2sts",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "WithB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fastenoff",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "17-20-21)sts",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "WithB",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Placesecondsetof",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "AllSizes",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fastenoff",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "COLLAR",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "joinBat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Turn.38(41",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "32-34-38",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "N4W3H3",
            "label": "ORG"
        }
    ]
}