{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nCROCHET COASTAL GRANNY HALTER-TOP RHC0130-036287M | February 23, 2024\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nABBREVIATIONS\nApprox = PM = Place Marker Sl st = Slip stitch\nApproximately Rep = Repeat Sp(s) = Space(s)\nBeg = Beginning Rnd(s) = Round(s) St(s) = Stitch(es)\nCh = Chain(s) RS = Right side Tog = Together\nDc = Double crochet Sc = Single crochet WS = Wrong side\nSIZES Notes:\nTo fit chest measurement • Motifs begin (beg) with Color 1\nXS/S/M 28-38\" [71-96.5 cm] (shortest color repeat (rep)) from\nL/XL 40-46\" [101.5-117 cm] center of pull-skein, leaving a 4\"\n2/3XL 48-54\" [122-134 cm] [10 cm] tail to weave in.\n• Each color aligns with 1 round\nFinished Garment diagonal (rnd) in the Motif with 5 colors\nmeasure, excluding ties in total. If too much color is left\nXS/S/M 8½\" [72.5 cm] at end of rnd, pull back some\nL/XL 34\" [86. cm] stitches (sts) and slightly loosen\n2/3XL 40\" [101.5 cm] gauge to re-work sts and finish\nat color change. If too little color\nGAUGE\nis left, pull back some sts and\nMotif = Approximately (approx) 6\"\nMATERIALS slightly tighten gauge to re-work\n[15 cm] square.\nSizes XS/S/M L/XL 2/3XL sts and finish at color change.\nRed Heart® All-in-One Granny Square™ (8.8 oz/250 g; 417 yds/381 m) INSTRUCTIONS • When Motif is complete, cut yarn\nContrast A 1 1 1 ball The instructions are written for where Color 5 (longest color rep)\nsmallest size. If changes are necessary ends, leaving a tail for weaving\nAran- Soft Sky (2011) 9 9 9 Granny Squares\nfor larger sizes the instructions will be in. Begin next Motif with Color 1\nRed Heart® Super Saver™ (7 oz/198 g; 364 yds/333 m)\nwritten thus XS/S/M (L/XL-2/3XL). and rep 5 rnds for each Motif.\nContrast B 1 1 2 ball(s)\nNumbers for each size are shown\nAran (313) 77/71 237/217 450/411 yds/m\nin the same color throughout the\nSize U.S. I/9 (5.5 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume® crochet hook or size needed\npattern. When only one number is\nto obtain gauge. Susan Bates® yarn needle. Susan Bates® stitch markers.\ngiven in black, it applies to all sizes.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET COASTAL GRANNY HALTER-TOP 1 of 3\nCROCHET COASTAL GRANNY HALTER-TOP RHC0130-036287M | February 23, 2024\nTOP 4th and 5th rnds: Sl st in ch-3 sp. Note: Keep working yarn to WS of Back Ties\nMOTIF Ch 6. 3 dc in same ch-3 sp. *(Ch 1. work so only flat sl st chain is visible Join A with sl st to any corner ch-3\nMake 9. 3 dc) in each ch-1 sp to next ch-3 on RS. sp. Ch 43 (53-63).\nNotes: sp. Ch 1.** (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) in next 1st row: 1 sc in 2nd ch from hook.\n• Chain (ch) 3 at beg of rnd counts ch-3 sp. Rep from * twice more, Edging 1 sc in each ch to end of chain.\nas double crochet (dc). then from * to ** once. 2 dc in first See diagram on page 3. Join with sl st to same ch-3 sp.\n• Ch 6 at beg of rnds counts as dc ch-3 sp. Join. 1st rnd: (RS). Join B with sl st to any Fasten off.\nand ch-3 space (s). Fasten off. corner ch-3 sp of Top. Ch 3 (counts Rep in ch-3 sp on opposite side\n• Join all rnds with slip stitch as 1 dc). 2 dc in same ch-3 sp. of Top for 2nd Back Tie.\n(sl st) to 3rd ch of ch-6 unless Assembly [*Ch 1. 3 dc in next ch-1 or ch-3 sp.* Weave in ends.\notherwise indicated. Seaming with Flat Sl St Join: (RS). Rep from * to * to next corner. Ch 1.\nWith B, sl st Motifs together (tog), (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) in corner ch-3 sp] Assembly\nWith A, starting with color 1, ch 4. working through the back loops 3 times. Rep from * to * to last With WS facing and Back Ties\nJoin with sl st to first ch to form only and keeping working yarn corner. (3 dc. Ch 3) in corner ch-3 on either side, fold top corner\nring. See diagram on page 3. to the wrong side (WS) of work to sp. Join with sl st to top of first ch-3. down 5 (7-9)\" [12.5 (18-23) cm]\n1st rnd: [Right side (RS)]. Ch 6. create a flat sl st chain detail on RS 2nd rnd: Loosely sl st in each of to WS.\n(3 dc. Ch 3) 3 times in ring. 2 dc in of work (see diagram). Join Motifs next 2 dc and ch-1 sp. Ch 3. 2 dc in With B, sew folded corner\nring. Join. into 3 horizontal strips, having 3 same ch-1 sp. [*Ch 1. 3 dc in next to Top, leaving approx 1½\"\n2nd rnd: Sl st in ch-3 sp. Ch 6. 3 dc motifs in each strip and following ch-1 sp.* Rep from * to * to next [4 cm] open for Neck Tie casing.\nin same ch-3 sp. *Ch 1. (3 dc. Ch 3. assembly diagram. Join 3 strips tog. corner. Ch 1. (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) in Feed Neck Tie through casing,\n3 dc) in next ch-3 sp. Rep from * corner ch-3 sp] 4 times. Ch 1. Join leaving equal amount of Neck Tie\ntwice more. Ch 1. 2 dc in first ch-3 with sl st to top of first ch-3. showing on both sides.\nsp. Join. Rep 2nd rnd 0 (3-7) times more.\n3rd rnd: Sl st in ch-3 sp. Ch 6. 3 dc Fasten off.\nin same ch-3 sp. *Ch 1. 3 dc in next\nch-1 sp. Ch 1. (3 dc. Ch 3. 3 dc) in Neck Tie\nnext ch-3 sp. Rep from * twice With A, ch 125.\nmore. Ch 1. 3 dc in last ch-1 sp. 1st row: *1 single crochet (sc)\nCh 1. 2 dc in first ch-3 sp. Join. in 2nd ch from hook. 1 sc in each\nFLAT SL ST JOINING DIAGRAM ch to end of chain. Fasten off.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET COASTAL GRANNY HALTER-TOP 2 of 3\nCROCHET COASTAL GRANNY HALTER-TOP RHC0130-036287M | February 23, 2024\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET COASTAL GRANNY HALTER-TOP 3 of 3"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY HALTER-TOP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "February 23, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Approx",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Marker Sl",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Approximately Rep = Repeat",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Color 1\nXS/S/M 28-38",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "71-96.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "L/XL 40-46",
            "label": "EVENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "101.5-117 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "122",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Finished Garment",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M 8½",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "72.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "L/XL 34",
            "label": "EVENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "86",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2/3XL 40",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "101.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sizes XS/S/M L/XL",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "8.8 oz/250",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "417",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Color 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "Soft Sky",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2011",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "9",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Granny Squares",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7 oz/198",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "364",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M (L/XL-2/3XL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Aran",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "313",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "237/217 450/411",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size U.S.",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "5.5 mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "only one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY HALTER-TOP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY HALTER-TOP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "February 23, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "53-63",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 1st",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Chain",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Edging 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Join",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "12.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18-23",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "RS 2nd",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck Tie",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Feed Neck Tie",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck Tie",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd 0",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 3",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck Tie",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "125",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY HALTER-TOP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY HALTER-TOP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "February 23, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY HALTER-TOP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}