{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nCROCHET MESH COVER-UP CAC0814-37830M | December 12, 2024\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: BEGINNER\nABBREVIATIONS\nApprox = Approximately Pat = Pattern\nBeg = Beginning PM = Place marker\nCh = Chain(s) Rep = Repeat\nDc = Double crochet RS = Right side\nFsc = (Foundation single Sp(s) = Space(s)\ncrochet). *Insert hook in “chain” St(s) = Stitch(es)\nof previous stitch and draw up Tog = Together\na loop. Yoh and draw through WS = Wrong side\n1 loop on hook (the “chain”). Yoh Yoh = Yarn over hook\nand draw through both loops\non hook. Repeat from * for\nindicated number of stitches.\nNote: A foundation single crochet\nconsists of a base chain and a\nsingle crochet worked at same\ntime\nSIZES GAUGE\nTo fit chest measurement 14 stitches (sts) and 5 rows = 4\" [10\nMATERIALS XS/S/M 28-38\" [71-96.5 cm] cm] in Mesh pattern (pat).\nL/XL/2XL 40-50\" [101.5-127 cm]\nCaron® Funfetti Cakes™ (8 oz/227 g; 239 yds/218 m)\n3/4/5XL 52-62\" [132-157.5 cm]\nSizes XS/S/M L/XL/2XL 3/4/5XL\nPink Frosting 3 4 6 balls\nFinished chest measurement\n(10023) 700/640 946/865 1196/1093 yds/m XS/S/M 43½\" [110.5 cm]\nSize U.S. I/9 (5.5 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume® crochet hook or size XL/2XL 55½\" [141 cm]\nneeded to obtain gauge. Susan Bates® yarn needle. Susan Bates® 3/4/5XL 65\" [165 cm]\nstitch markers. (according to schematic)\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET MESH COVER-UP 1 of 2\nCROCHET MESH COVER-UP CAC0814-37830M | December 12, 2024\nINSTRUCTIONS SLEEVES (Make 2 alike) PM 7½ (10-11¼)\" [19 (25.5-28.5)\n10¼ - 10¾ - 11 5¾ - 8½ - 11¾\nThe instructions are written for size Ch 56 (74-83) [multiple of 3 ch +5]. cm] down each side edge from\nXS/S/M. If changes are necessary for Rep from ** to ** as given for Front shoulder seam for armholes. Sew\n8½ SLEEVE 7½\nlarger sizes the instructions will be and Back. bottom of Sleeves around armhole\n8½ 10\nwritten XS/S/M (L/XL/2X-3/4/5XL). 17 (23-26) ch-2 sps. 18 (24-27) dc. o7p½ening, between armhole 11¼\nWhen only one number is given, it Rep last row until Sleeve measures markers.\napplies to all sizes. 8½ (8½-7½)\" [21.5 (21.5-19) cm]. PM 10\" [25.5 cm] up each side edge\nFasten off. from bottom for side slits. Sew\n14¾ - 20 - 22½\nNote: Chain (ch) 5 at beginning sleeve and side seams to markers\n(beg) of row counts as double BELT for slits. Weave in ends. 34\n36\ncrochet (dc) and ch-2 space (sp). Ch 2. Weave Belt through ch-2 sps that FRONT and BACK\n38\n1st row: Insert hook in 2nd chain sit at natural waist (try on Cover-Up\nFRONT & BACK (Make 2 alike). from hook and draw up a loop. to mark these sps). Ends of Belt\nCh 80 (101-125) [multiple of 3 ch Yarn over hook (yoh) and draw meet at center front.\n+5]. through 1 loop on hook. Yoh and\n**1st row: [Right Side (RS)]. 1 dc in draw through both loops on hook\n8th ch from hook (counts as - 1 foundation single crochet (fsc) 10\nskipped 2 ch, 1 dc, and ch-2). *Ch 2. made. Work 142 (181-220) more\nSkip next 2 ch. 1 dc in next ch. fsc. Fasten off.\nRepeat (rep) from * to end of chain. Tie knot approx 1\" [2.5 cm] in from 21¾ - 27¾ - 34½\nTurn. 25 (32-40) ch-2 sps. 26 (33- each end of Belt.\n41) dc.\n2nd row: Ch 5 (counts as dc and FINISHING\nch-2 sp here and throughout). Skip Place markers (PM) 5¾ (8½-11¾)\" 10¼ - 10¾ - 11 5¾ - 8½ - 11¾\nnext ch-2 sp. 1 dc in next dc. *Ch 2. [14.5 (21.5-30) cm] in from each\nSkip next ch-2 sp. 1 dc in next dc. side edge for Neck Opening. With 8½ SLEEVE 7½\nRep from * to end of row. Turn.** Wrong Sides (WS) of Front and 8½ 10\nRep last row until work from beg Back together (tog), using flat 7½ 11¼\nmeasures 34 (36-38)\" [86.5 (91.5- seam, sew shoulder seams from\n96.5) cm]. markers to side edges.\nFasten off.\n14¾ - 20 - 22½\n34\n36\nFRONT and BACK\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET MESH COVER-UP 2 of 2 38\n10\n21¾ - 27¾ - 34½"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "MESH COVER-UP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "December 12, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Pat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fsc",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Foundation",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "14",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "71-96.5 cm] cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Mesh",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "101.5-127 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "8",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "239",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3/4/5XL",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "52-62",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "132",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 4 6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1196/1093",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M 43½",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "110.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5.5 mm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "141 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3/4/5XL 65",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "165 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET MESH COVER-UP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "December 12, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "PM 7½",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "10-11¼",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "19",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "25.5-28.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10¼ - 10¾ - 11",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 56",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "74-83",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M.",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M (L/XL/2X-3/4/5XL",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "23",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24-27",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "only one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sleeve",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "21.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "21.5-19",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "PM 10",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "25.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "14¾ - 20 - 22½",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "34",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "36",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "FRONT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "BACK",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "38\n1st",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Insert",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "FRONT & BACK",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "101-125",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "as - 1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "fsc",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "142",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "181",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "fsc",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "21¾ - 27¾",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "25",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "32-40",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "26",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Belt",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "41",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 5",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "8½-11¾",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10¼ - 10¾ - 11",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "14.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "21.5-30",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Neck Opening",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "34",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "36-38",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "86.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "91.5-",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "96.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "14¾ - 20 - 22½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "34",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "FRONT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "CROCHET MESH COVER-UP",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2 38",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}