{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nCROCHET GRANNY JACKET Designed by Sarah Zimmerman of Repeat Crafter Me CAC0333-029267M | August 10, 2020\nSarah Zimmerman\nfrom Repeat Crafter Me\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nABBREVIATIONS\nBeg = Beginning Rnd(s) = Round(s)\nCh = Chain(s) Sl st = Slip stitch\nCont = Continue(ity) Sp(s) = Space(s)\nDc = Double crochet St(s) = Stitch(es)\nRep = Repeat Tog = Together\nSIZE\nOne size to fit child ages 4 to 8. **1st rnd: Ch 3. 2 dc in ring. Ch 2.\n(3 dc in ring. Ch 2) 3 times. Join\nGAUGE with sl st to first st. Sl st into first\n12 sc and 13 rows = 4\" [10 cm]. ch-2 sp.\n2nd rnd: Ch 3. (2 dc. Ch 2. 3 dc) all\nINSTRUCTIONS in first ch-2 sp. [(Ch 1. 3 dc. Ch 2 .\nNote: Ch 3 at beg of rnd counts 3 dc) all in next ch-2 sp] 3 times.\nas dc. All rnds are joined with sl st Ch 1. Join. Sl st into first ch-2 sp.\nto first st. 3rd rnd: Ch 3. (2 dc. Ch 2. 3 dc) all\nMATERIALS\nin first corner ch-2 sp. Ch 1. 3 dc\nCaron® Jumbo Ombre™ (12 oz/340 g; 595 yds/544 m)\nSMALL GRANNY SQUARES in next ch-1 sp. *(Ch 1. 3 dc. Ch 2.\nWhite Water (19007) 2 balls (make 4) 3 dc) all in next in corner ch-2 sp.\nSize U.S. H/8 (5 mm) crochet hook or size needed to obtain gauge. See diagram on page 3. Ch 1. 3 dc in next ch-1 sp. Rep from *\nTapestry needle. Beg using magic loop method, around. Join. Sl st into next ch-2 sp.\ndemonstrated here.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY JACKET Designed by Sarah Zimmerman of Repeat Crafter Me 1 of 3\nCROCHET GRANNY JACKET Designed by Sarah Zimmerman of Repeat Crafter Me CAC0333-029267M | August 10, 2020\n4th rnd: Ch 3. (2 dc. Ch 2. 3 dc) all Once all seams marked in red are\nin first corner ch-2 sp. (Ch 1. 3 dc sewn, fold so points A and B meet. C\nB\nin next ch-1 sp) twice. *(Ch 1. 3 dc. Stitch from A/B to C to complete AA B\nCh 2. 3 dc) all in next in corner Hood seam. A C\nch-2 sp. (Ch 1. 3 dc in next ch-1\nsp) twice. Rep from * around. SLEEVES\nJoin. Sl st into next ch-2 sp. Join yarn with sl st io any ch-sp\n5th rnd: Ch 3. (2 dc. Ch 2. 3 dc) all along armhole.\nin first corner ch-2 sp. (Ch 1. 3 dc 1st rnd: Ch 3. 2 dc in ch-sp. Ch 1.\nin next ch-1 sp) 3 times. *(Ch 1. *3 dc in next ch-sp. Ch 1. Rep from *\n3 dc. Ch 2. 3 dc) all in next in corner around. Join with sl st to first st. Sl st\nch-2 sp. (Ch 1. 3 dc in next ch-1 sp) to next ch-sp.\n3 times. Rep from * around. Join. 2nd rnd: Cont as established in first\nSl st into next ch-2 sp. Fasten off.** rnd, working (3 dc. Ch 1) in each ch-\nsp\nLARGE GRANNY SQUARES (make 3rd to 18th rnds: As 2nd rnd.\n3) 19th rnd: Ch 1. Work 2 sc in each\nWork as for Small Granny Squares ch-1 sp around. Join.\nfrom ** to **. 20th to 24th rnds: Ch 1. 1 sc in\neach sc around. Join.\n5th to 10th rnds: Cont as Fasten off and weave in ends.\nestablished, working (Ch 1. 3 dc.\nAssembly Diagram\nCh 2. 3 dc) in each corner ch-2 sp, Add Length to Bottom of Jacket\nand working (Ch 1. 3 dc) in each (optional) 2nd row: Ch 3. 3 dc in first ch-1 sp. Add Width to Bottom of Jacket\nch-1 sp. Fasten off. Join yarn with sl st to bottom corner Ch 1. *3 dc in next ch-1 sp. Ch 1. (optional)\nof Jacket to work along bottom Rep from * to end of row, working Join yarn with sl st to bottom corner\nAssemble Body edge. 1 dc in last st. Turn.*** of Jacket to work across Fronts and\nLay out granny squares according ***1st row: Ch 3. 3 dc in first ch-sp. Hood of Jacket.\nto Assembly Diagram and stitch tog Ch 1. *3 dc in next ch-sp. Ch 1. Rep Cont as established until Jacket\nwith tapestry needle as indicated from * to end of row, working 1 dc reaches desired length. Fasten off. Work from *** to *** as given for\nwith red lines. Leave sections in last st. Turn. Bottom of Jacket until desired\nmarked with green lines open for width is reached. Fasten off.\narmholes.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY JACKET Designed by Sarah Zimmerman of Repeat Crafter Me 2 of 3\nCROCHET GRANNY JACKET Designed by Sarah Zimmerman of Repeat Crafter Me CAC0333-029267M | August 10, 2020\nGRANNY SQUARE\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. CROCHET GRANNY JACKET Designed by Sarah Zimmerman of Repeat Crafter Me 3 of 3"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sarah Zimmerman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "August 10, 2020",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sarah Zimmerman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Repeat Crafter Me",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "crochet St(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "SIZE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ages 4 to 8",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "13",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Jumbo Ombre",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "595",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "White Water",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "19007",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "crochet",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sarah Zimmerman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sarah Zimmerman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "August 10, 2020",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 dc",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Cont",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd to 18th",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "19th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "20th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "24th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Cont",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Assembly Diagram",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Add Length",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Add Width",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 1",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Jacket",
            "label": "EVENT"
        },
        {
            "text": "1 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Assembly Diagram",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "stitch tog Ch 1",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sarah Zimmerman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sarah Zimmerman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "August 10, 2020",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sarah Zimmerman",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}