{
    "title": "RED HEART® Boutique™ Midnight™: 4 balls 1944",
    "steps": [
        "RED HEART® Boutique™ Midnight™: 4 balls 1944\nHarvest Moon.\nCrochet Hook: 6.5mm [US K-10½].\nStitch markers, yarn needle.\nGAUGE: Gauge is not critical for this project.\nNOTE: Front and Back pieces are worked from side to side.\nTUNIC\nFront and Back (both alike)\nCh 105.\nRow 1: Hdc in 2nd ch from hook and in each ch across –\n104 hdc.\nRow 2-44: Ch 2, (counts as hdc here and throughout),\nturn, hdc in next hdc, [ch 15, skip next 15 hdc, hdc in next\n2 hdc] 6 times – 6 ch-15 spaces.\nRow 45: Ch 2, hdc in each hdc and ch across.\nFasten off.\nFINISHING\nLeft Shoulder\nWith right sides together, measure and mark 6” from\nfirst and last rows along side edges for Shoulders. Sew\nShoulder seams.\nMeasure and mark 16” down from Shoulders along first\nand last rows for Armholes. Sew next 12” along side\nseams closed, leaving remaining side edge unsewn.\nDrop Stitch Tunic Weave in ends.\nJazz up your wardrobe with this fun crocheted RED HEART® Boutique™ Midnight™\nArt. E786, Available in 2.5 oz (70g),\ntunic. It’s fast to make with no shaping and the\n153 yd (140m) balls.\nback and front are exactly the same. You’ll want\none in several colors.\nABBREvIATIONS: ch = chain; hdc = half double crochet;\nmm = millimeters; [ ] = work directions in brackets the\nLW2898\nnumber of times specified.\nDesigned by Double Stitch Twins.\nOne size fits most.\nTunic measures 26” wide x 30” long.\nFor more ideas & inspiration -\n©2011 Coats & Clark\nwww.redheart.com\nP.O. Box 12229\nGreenville, SC 29612-0229 www.crochettoday.com www.knittingtodaymag.com"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "RED HEART® Boutique",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1944",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Harvest Moon",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "6.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Gauge",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Front and Back",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "105",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "104",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "15",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 15",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "ch-15",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "45",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shoulders",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shoulders",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Armholes",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 12",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Drop Stitch Tunic Weave",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "RED HEART® Boutique",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2.5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "70",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "140",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "26",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "30",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2011",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "P.O. Box",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        }
    ]
}