{
    "title": "GAUGE: 11 dc = 4”; 4 rows = 4”. CHECK YOUR GAUGE. Use",
    "steps": [
        "GAUGE: 11 dc = 4”; 4 rows = 4”. CHECK YOUR GAUGE. Use\nany size hook to obtain the gauge.\nNOTE: Fringe can be added to any heavyweight skirt.\nSKIRT\nBase Stitches\nWith right side facing and 1 strand of A, sew a straight line\nof running stitches along lower edge of skirt with each stitch\nmeasuring ½” long. Knot ends securely.\nWith B, sew a second line of running stitches ½” above the\nprevious line. Knot ends securely.\nWith A, sew a third line of running stitches ½” above the previous\nline. Knot ends securely.\nLower Fringe\nRound 1: Join A in 1 base stitch at center of back of skirt, ch 3\n(counts as dc here and throughout), 2 dc in same space, 3 dc in\neach base stitch around, slip st in top of beginning ch to join.\nRound 2: Ch 2 (counts as hdc here and throughout), hdc in each\ndc around, slip st in top of beginning ch.\nRound 3: [Ch 20, slip st in next hdc] around.\nFasten off.\nCenter Fringe\nRound 1: Join B in 1 base stitch at center of back of skirt, ch 3\n(counts as dc here and throughout), 2 dc in same space, 3 dc in\neach base stitch around, slip st in top of beginning ch to join.\nRound 2: Ch 2 (counts as hdc here and throughout), hdc in each\ndc around, slip st in top of beginning ch.\nRound 3: [Ch 20, slip st in next hdc] around.\nFasten off.\nTop Fringe\nDiva Denim Remix Skirt\nRound 1: Join A in 1 base stitch at center of back of skirt, ch 2\n(counts as hdc here and throughout), 2 hdc in same space, 3 hdc\nin each base stitch around, slip st in top of beginning ch to join.\nTransform a skirt from plain to lively and fun with\nRound 2: [Ch 15, slip st in next hdc] around.\nrows of crocheted ruffles. We show it in denim, Fasten off.\nbut other fabric skirts work just as well.\nFINISHING\nWeave in ends.\nLW2471\nRED HEART® “Soft Yarn”, Art. E728\navailable in solid color 5 oz (140 g),\nDesigned by Double Stitch Twins. 256 yd (234 m), print 4 oz (113 g), 204 yd\n(187 m), and heathers 4oz, (113g) 212 yd\nFringe measures 4” long and adds 2” to skirt length. (194m) balls.\nRED HEART® “Soft Yarn”: 1 ball each 9820 Mid Blue A and\n9440 Light Grey Heather B. ABBREvIATIONS: A, B, C = Color A, B, C; ch = chain; dc =\ndouble crochet; hdc = half double crochet; mm = millimeters;\nCrochet Hook: 6mm [US J-10]. st(s) = stitch(es); [ ] = work directions in brackets the number of\nHeavyweight skirt, yarn needle. times specified.\nFor more ideas & inspiration -\n©2011 Coats & Clark\nwww.redheart.com\nP.O. Box 12229\nGreenville, SC 29612-0229 www.crochettoday.com www.knittingtodaymag.com"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "11",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "½",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "second",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "½",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "third",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "½",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "Lower Fringe\nRound 1: Join A",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Center Fringe\nRound 1",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Top Fringe\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Diva Denim Remix Skirt\nRound 1",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Round 2",
            "label": "PRODUCT"
        },
        {
            "text": "Ch 15",
            "label": "LAW"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Art",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "E728",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "140",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Stitch Twins",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "256 yd",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "234",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "113",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "204 yd\n",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "187",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "heathers 4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "113",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "212",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "194",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9820",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Mid Blue A",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "9440",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Grey Heather B.",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "mm =",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crochet Hook",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "US",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2011",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "P.O. Box",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Greenville",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "SC",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "29612-0229",
            "label": "DATE"
        }
    ]
}