{
    "title": "GRANNY CROCHET SHORTS CAC0114-034400M | January 31, 2023",
    "steps": [
        "GRANNY CROCHET SHORTS CAC0114-034400M | January 31, 2023\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nABBREVIATIONS\nBeg = Begin(ning)(s) Rnd(s) = Round(s)\nCh = Chain(s) RS = Right side\nDc = Double crochet Sc = Single crochet\nDc4tog = (Yoh and draw up a Sc2tog = Draw up a loop in\nloop in next stitch. Yoh and draw each of next 2 sc. Yoh and draw\nthrough 2 loops on hook) 4 times. through all 3 loops on hook\nYoh and draw through all 5 loops Sl st = Slip stitch\non hook Sp(s) = Space(s)\nHdc = Half double crochet St(s) = Stitch(es)\nPM = Place marker Tog = Together\nRep = Repeat Yoh = Yarn over hook\nSIZES INSTRUCTIONS\nTo fit hip measurement The instructions are written for\n(Shorts are designed to stretch smallest size. If changes are\nslightly to fit) necessary for larger sizes the\nMATERIALS\nXS/S/M 34-38\" [86.5-96.5 cm] instructions will be written thus ( ).\nCaron® Simply Soft™ (6 oz/170.1 g/315 yds/288 m)\nL/XL 40-46\" [101.5-117 cm] Numbers for each size are shown\nSizes XS/S/M L/XL 2/3/4XL 2/3/4XL 48-54\" [122-137 cm] in the same color throughout the\nMain Color (MC) Black (39727) 1 2 2 ball(s) pattern. When only one number is\nGAUGES\ngiven in black, it applies to all sizes.\nContrast A Strawberry (COL0015) 1 1 1 ball\n16 sc and 17 rows = 4\" [10 cm]\nContrast B Soft Blue (39712) 1 1 1 ball\nMotif = 3½\" [9 cm] square. Note: Ch 3 at beg of rnd counts\nContrast C Gold (39782) 1 1 1 ball\nas dc.\nContrast D Orchid (39717) 1 1 1 ball\nSize U.S. G/6 (4 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume™ crochet hook or size\nneeded to obtain gauge. Susan Bates® stitch markers. Susan Bates®\nyarn needle.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. GRANNY CROCHET SHORTS 1 of 3\nGRANNY CROCHET SHORTS CAC0114-034400M | January 31, 2023\nMOTIF 4th rnd: Ch 3. 2 dc around post of Next row: Ch 1. Sc2tog. 1 sc in Shape back Waistband: 1st rnd:\nMake 24 (30-48). joining hdc. *(3 dc in next ch-3 sp) each sc to last 2 sc. Sc2tog. Turn. Join MC with sl st to side seam of\ntwice.** (3 dc. Ch 2. 3 dc) in next 10 sts. shorts. Ch 1. 1 sc in same sp as sl st\nMake 6 (7-12) Motifs, having A as ch-3 sp. Rep from * twice more, Next 2 rows: Ch 1. 1 sc in each sc and each of next 47 (59-71) dc. PM\nColor 1. then from * to ** once. 3 dc in first to end of row. Turn. on last sc. 1 sc in each of next 48\nMake 6 (7-12) Motifs, having B as sp. Ch 2. Join with sl st to top of Rep last 3 rows until there are 4 sts. (60-72) dc. Join with sl st to first sc.\nColor 1. ch-3. 4 groups of 3-dc between PM for beg of rnd.\nMake 6 (8-12) Motifs, having C as corner ch-3 sps. Fasten off. Next row: Ch 1. 1 sc in first sc. 2nd rnd: Ch 1. 1 sc in each of first\nColor 1. Sc2tog. 1 sc in last sc. Turn. 3 sts. 10 sc. 1 hdc in each of next 7 sc.\nMake 6 (8-12) Motifs, having D as Crotch Gusset Next row: Ch 1. 1 sc in each of 1 dc in each of next 14 (26-38) sc.\nColor 1. Note: Each edge of Crotch Gusset next 3 sts. Fasten off. 1 hdc in each of next 7 sc. 1 sc in\nshould match length of side of each sc to end of rnd. Join with sl st\nWith Color 1, ch 4. Join with sl st to Motif. FINISHING to first sc.\nfirst ch to form a ring. See diagram Following Diagram on page 3, sew 3rd rnd: Ch 1. 1 sc in each of first\non page 3. With MC, ch 4. 8 (10-12) Motifs tog into Strips. 7 sc. 1 hdc in each of next 7 sts.\n1st rnd: Ch 3. 3 dc in ring. (Ch 2. 1st row: (RS). 1 sc in 2nd ch from Sew 2 (2-3) Strips tog into top 1 dc in each of next 20 (32-44) sts.\n4 dc) 3 times in ring. Ch 2. Join with hook. 1 sc in each of next 2 ch. section of Shorts. Sew back seam. 1 hdc in each of next 7 sts. 1 sc in\nsl st to top of ch-3. Fasten off. Turn. 3 sc. each sc to end of rnd. Join with sl st\n2nd rnd: Join MC with sl st to any 2nd row: Ch 1. 1 sc in first sc. 2 sc Sew 4 (5-6) Motifs tog into Strip to first sc.\nch-2 sp. Ch 1. (1 sc. Ch 2. 1 sc) in in next sc. 1 sc in last sc. Turn. 4 sc. for each Leg. Sew Leg Strips to top 4th rnd: Ch 1. 1 sc in each of first\nsame sp as sl st. *Ch 2. Dc4tog. 3rd and 4th rows: Ch 1. 1 sc in section of Shorts, leaving opening 3 sc. 1 hdc in each of next 7 sts.\nCh 2. (1 sc. Ch 2. 1 sc) in next ch-2 each sc to end of row. Turn. for Crotch Gusset. Following 1 dc in each of next 28 (40-52) sts.\nsp. Rep from * twice more. Ch 2. 5th row: Ch 1. 2 sc in first sc. 1 sc diagram, sew Crotch Gusset into 1 hdc in each of next 7 sts. 1 sc in\nDc4tog. Ch 1. Join with sc in top in each sc to last sc. 2 sc in last sc. position between Leg Motifs. each sc to end of rnd. Join with sl st\nof first sc. Turn. to first sc.\n3rd rnd: Ch 1. 1 sc around post of Rep last 3 rows until there are Leg edging: 1st rnd: (RS). Join 5th and 6th rnds: Ch 3. 1 dc in\njoining sc. *Ch 3. 1 sc in next ch-2 12 sc. MC with sl st to inner side seam. each st around. Join with sl st to\nsp. Rep from * around. Ch 1. Join Ch 1. Work sc around leg opening, first dc.\nwith hdc in top of first sc. Next 4 rows: Ch 1. 1 sc in each sc working 1 sc in each dc, corner Fasten off.\nto end of row. Turn. ch-2 sps and joining sp. Join with\nsl st to first sc. Fasten off.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. GRANNY CROCHET SHORTS 2 of 3\nGRANNY CROCHET SHORTS XS/S/M L/XL CAC0114-034400M | January 31, 2023\nWaist cord: First st: With MC,\nXS/S/M L/XL\nch 2. Draw up a loop in 2nd ch from\nhook. Yoh and draw through 1 loop\non hook - chain made. Yoh and draw\nthrough 2 loops on hook - sc made.\nKey\n2/3/4XL\nRemaining sts: *Draw up a loop in\n= MC\n“chain” of previous st. Yoh and draw\nthrough 1 loop on hook (chain). Yoh Key = A\n2/3/4XL\nand draw through 2 loops on hook.\n== M BC\nRep from * until Cord measures\nlength to fit waist measurement == A C\nand approx. 12\" [30.5 cm] extra == B D\nlength for tie. Fasten off.\n= C\nBeg at center front, thread cord\nthrough 1st rnd of dc around = D\nWaistband.\nCrotch Gusset\n4\nSTITCH KEY\n3 Beg ch Last row\n= chain (ch)\n2 Crotch Gusset\n= slip stitch (sl st)\n1\n= single crochet (sc) Beg ch Last row\n= half double crochet (hdc)\n= double crochet (dc)\nBeg ch of Crotch Last row of Crotch\n= double crochet 4\ntogether (dc4tog)\nBeg ch of Crotch Last row of Crotch\nMOTIF\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. GRANNY CROCHET SHORTS 3 of 3"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "GRANNY CROCHET SHORTS CAC0114-034400M",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "January 31, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "marker Tog",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shorts",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "86.5-96.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Caron®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Simply Soft",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "6",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "g/315 yds/288 m",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "L/XL 40-46",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "101.5-117 cm] Numbers",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Sizes XS/S/M L/XL",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "48",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "122",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Main Color",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "39727",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "only one",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "16",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "9 cm] square",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "39782",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "39717",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Size U.S. G/6",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY CROCHET",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "January 31, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shape",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Waistband",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "30-48",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 10",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "shorts",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7-12",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 47",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "59-71",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 48",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "7-12",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "60-72",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3-dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "8-12",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Color 1. Sc2tog",
            "label": "WORK_OF_ART"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "8-12",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 14",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "26-38",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crotch Gusset",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motif",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Following Diagram",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4. 8",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "10-12",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Strips",
            "label": "FAC"
        },
        {
            "text": "7",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "32-44",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4 dc",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shorts",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Strip",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Leg Strips",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Shorts",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crotch Gusset",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "next 28",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "40-52",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crotch Gusset",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Leg Motifs",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "rnd",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "5th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6th",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3. 1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Fasten",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY CROCHET",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "SHORTS XS/S/M L/XL CAC0114-034400M",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "January 31, 2023",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Waist",
            "label": "NORP"
        },
        {
            "text": "First",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "XS/S/M L/XL\nch 2",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2/3/4XL",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Cord",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "12",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "30.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1st",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Waistband",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crotch Gusset\n",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3 Beg ch Last",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "slip stitch",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "half",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crotch Last row",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Crotch Last row",
            "label": "LOC"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "GRANNY CROCHET",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}