{
    "title": "SHOP KIT",
    "steps": [
        "SHOP KIT\nUPCYCLED CROCHET COLLAR RHC0840-37895M | December 13, 2024\nMEDIUM\n4\nCROCHET I SKILL LEVEL: EASY\nABBREVIATIONS\nApprox = Approximately Sc = Single crochet\nBeg = Begin(ing) Sl st = Slip stitch\nCh = Chain(s) Sp(s) = Space(s)\nPat = Pattern St(s) = Stitch(es)\nRep = Repeat WS = Wrong side\nSIZE • To make a custom Collar, every\nOne size to replace average Adult additional row of pat worked\nbutton-down shirt collar. Finished will add approx ½\" [1.25 cm] to\nsize approx 17\" x 2½\" [43 x 6.5 cm]. desired width.\n• Collar Edging will add approx ¼\"\nGAUGE [.75 cm] to total width.\n18 sts and 18 rows = 4\" [10 cm] in\nMoss Stitch Pattern (counting sc COLLAR\nand ch-1 sps). Ch 76 (multiple of 2 ch).\n1st row: (RS). 1 sc in 2nd ch from\nINSTRUCTIONS\nhook. *Ch 1. Skip next ch. 1 sc in\nNotes: next ch. Rep from * to end of row.\n• Instructions are written to make Turn.\na Collar measuring 17\" [43 cm] 2nd row: Ch 1. 1 sc in first sc. *1 sc\nlong. If you require a longer or in next ch-1 sp. Ch 1. Skip next sc.\nMATERIALS shorter Collar, adjust your Rep from * to last sc. 1 sc in last sc.\nRed Heart® Super Saver® Bitty Stripes™ (10 oz/283 g; 515 yds/471 m) starting chain accordingly, Turn.\nRainbow (0100) 1 ball or 56 yds/52 m making sure the number of 3rd row: Ch 1. 1 sc in first sc. *Ch 1.\nchains is divisible by 2. Skip next sc. 1 sc in next ch-1 sp.\nSize U.S. H/8 (5 mm) Susan Bates® Silvalume® crochet hook or\n• Collar width will measure approx Rep from * to last sc. 1 sc in last sc.\nsize needed to obtain gauge. Coats and Clark® Dual Duty XP®\n3\" [7.5 cm]. Turn.\nAll-Purpose Thread. Collared button-down shirt. Seam ripper.\nLast 2 rows form Moss Stitch Pat.\nStraight pins. Sewing machine.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. UPCYCLED CROCHET COLLAR 1 of 2\nUPCYCLED CROCHET COLLAR RHC0840-37895M | December 13, 2024\nWork in pat until Collar measures Pin Collar into place, making sure\napprox 2¾\" [7 cm], ending on a WS everything is nice and flat and\nrow. Fasten off. ends of crocheted Collar are\npositioned where the original\nEdging: With RS facing, join yarn collar was.\nto bottom right corner. Ch 1. Work\n1 sc into side of each row to top\ncorner. (1 sc. Ch 2. 1 sc) in first sc of\nlast row. Work in Moss St Pat to last\nsc. (1 sc. Ch 2. 1 sc) in last sc. Work\n1 sc into side of each row down left\nside to bottom corner.\nFasten off.\nWeave in ends.\nFINISHING\nUsing seam ripper, carefully remove\nfabric collar from the collar stand\nof shirt.\nEach end of fabric collar is secured\nAfter fabric collar has been\nby backstitching, which can be\nremoved, tidy it up by getting rid\ntricky to get into. Start about 1\" Using the stitching holes of the\nof any broken threads left in the\n[2.5 cm] away from end of collar original seam as a guide, sew Collar\nfabric.\nstand, picking apart enough into place with sewing machine\nWith the inside of shirt facing up,\nstitches to fit stitch ripper into through all thicknesses. For best\nplace crocheted Collar between\nseam. results, sew this seam with inside\nfront and back pieces of shirt collar\nof shirt facing up, going slowly to\nstand, with RS facing you and\nensure a nice tidy seam.\napprox ½\" [1.25 cm] of crocheted\nCollar down from top edge of\nstand.\nFor accessibility support, please contact customer care at 1-888-368-8401 or access@yarnspirations.com. UPCYCLED CROCHET COLLAR 2 of 2"
    ],
    "entities": [
        {
            "text": "KIT",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "December 13, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Approximately",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Beg",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Space(s",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Pat = Pattern",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "One",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Adult",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1.25 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2½",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "43",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "6.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Collar Edging",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "GAUGE",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "18",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "4",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "10 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Moss Stitch Pattern",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "76",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2nd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "17",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "43 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Bitty Stripes",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "10",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "515",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Turn",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Rainbow",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "56",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "3rd",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "U.S.",
            "label": "GPE"
        },
        {
            "text": "5",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Susan Bates",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Silvalume®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "• Collar",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Coats",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Clark®",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "3",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "7.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Last 2",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Moss Stitch Pat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "December 13, 2024",
            "label": "DATE"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "Pin Collar",
            "label": "ORG"
        },
        {
            "text": "7 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "first",
            "label": "ORDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "Moss St Pat",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "about 1",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2.5 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "approx ½",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1.25 cm",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "Collar",
            "label": "PERSON"
        },
        {
            "text": "1-888-368",
            "label": "QUANTITY"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        },
        {
            "text": "2",
            "label": "CARDINAL"
        }
    ]
}